I want to be paired up with the guy I like for practice!
I hope my baby is born safely
Please let me stay happy and healthy
What?!
I-I'm sorry! I tripped and...
Wait...
Watanabe-san?
Watanabe Akari and Sakurazaka Shiori...
I never imagined so many things would happen between the two of them and me.
Oh! Watanabe-san, are you here about your partner for the marriage practical?
No, I'm not.
I'm not!
"Marriage Practical"
The marriage practical.
An insane part of our high school's curriculum that's about to begin.
As the name implies, male-female pairs are chosen
to live together as a mock married couple.
Everyone in class is agitated because of it,
but that's not where my mind is right now.
Just a little more...
Just a little more, and my bride will be decided!
Come on, Chloris. Chloris!
Jiro
Yes!
Man, I envy you, Jiro-chan.
Imagine getting excited over a pixel art character in this day and age.
You've got it all wrong.
The fact that it's pixel art lets the imagination run free.
Just look at RotoSaGa. 7 is out, and it's got 3D views.
Observe the quality of the newest version of Princess Chloris!
Oh, shut up.
I like the simple innocence from back when they did 1.
I guess it does make it easier to imagine things...
But back in 1, you couldn't pick the heroine, right?
Hey.
You're in the way.
Watanabe Akari! She smells so nice.
She really is cute.
How, exactly?
The way she talks is so unendearing.
She shows so much skin, it's vulgar.
She treats us social outcasts like idiots.
I never, ever want to get involved with her type!
Minami-kun!
I saw you!
Tenjin Minami, huh?
The newspaper club interviewed you in the courtyard, right?
I'm a guy, but even I feel like I'll be purified by his sky-high ikemen level!
Oh, that. Yeah.
It's for the thing they're putting you on the cover of, right?
And he's a good guy on top of that.
Akari keeps saying they must be doing a special edition on ikemen.
For us shadow-dwellers, he's poison. No, he's absolute evil.
Wha?!
They wouldn't do that.
B-But Minami-kun, you're really cool, so...
Thanks. It makes me happy to hear that.
She's such an open book.
Talk about a complete 180.
Aw, crap.
Now I've gotta wait to meet my bride.
Jiro
Jiro-kun.
Huh?
It's finally time for the marriage practical, huh?
Yeah.
I feel sort of nervous.
Is it just me?
I'm not good with girls, so I'm nothing but nerves.
The only girl I can speak with normally
is my childhood friend and first love.
They say your first love never comes true,
but if things can stay like this between us forever, that's enough.
I get shy around strangers, so...
I hope I'm paired with someone I know well!
Y-Yeah.
Agency for Cultural Affairs Recommended Demonstration Program 2022
Marriage Practical Course Guidance Video
Now, everyone, pay attention. I'm going to begin the explanation.
Starting now, you will each live as a pair with your partner in the training dorm.
It's furnished and has a kitchen,
so there's no need to worry about day-to-day matters.
The sensor installed in the living room will continuously monitor your lifestyle and actions.
Practical Points
And here is the most important thing...
As you are all still students, your bedrooms are separate.
Fingerprint verification ensures that only the room's occupant may enter.
Do not get carried away.
Keep yourselves firmly under control.
What the heck?
Why even make us do this, then?
One more thing. Regarding the A-rank system...
There are fifteen guys and girls in each of the five classes,
Every month, those ranked in the top ten according to their grades...
meaning there's a 1-in-75 chance of being paired with any one person.
I hope I'm paired with someone I know well!
That's just a fantasy!
I'm her childhood friend!
She just finds me easy to talk to because she doesn't see me as a guy!
But if we get paired, then maybe...
I'll check my luck!
Jiro
If the hero defeats the boss alone with no damage taken,
he can take the side route to the heroine.
From there, if you go straight through the dungeon...
Lancia
Huh? Do you have a problem with me or something?
Lancia?!
No, no.
This has now purged all my bad luck.
Only good things can happen now.
Why is it you?!
Th-That's kind of what I'd like to ask!
What?!
Um, wait just a moment, please.
Let's calm down a bit.
Will you quit talking all formal? It's creeping me out.
S-Sorry. First, could you let me go?
Now you're too friendly all of a sudden!
You're being unfair.
What a buzzkill. This sucks!
How'd they come up with this pairing, anyway?
It makes no sense at all.
I'm a victim here, too.
What was that?!
It-It's just... It seems like you had a preferred partner in mind,
and I had someone I wanted to be paired with, too. That's all I meant.
It's gotta be Sakurazaka-san, right?
BULL'S
EYE
You're so easy to read! How stupid can you be?
There's no way she'd ever give you the time of day.
I don't want to hear that from you!
I mean, she's a little plain, but she's cute.
What're you gonna do?
Things might be going really well for her right now.
Please, be gentle.
M-M-M-Making such wild speculations is disrespectful toward her, I feel.
Killjoy.
S-So what if I am?
Oh, crap!
If we don't get along, we lose points!
Then we might get to minus 10,000.
Cut the shit!
Get along with me!
Right now!
But that attitude! That behavior!
We'll increase our points, get to A-rank, and change our pairing!
Ow!
Is that even possible?
Didn't you hear the explanation? I can't believe you.
Look at this.
Seishun Academy Third-Years' Marriage Practical Manual
1-2 At the end of every month, those who score in the top ten (A-rank) will be granted the right to change pairings among themselves. In such cases, the consent of everyone involved is required. 2 Regarding Scoring 2-1 Totals will be reset at the end of the month, and each month will start at 0 points.
"At the end of every month, those who score in the top ten (A-rank)
will be granted the right to change pairings among themselves."
For real?
Minami-kun would never be anything less than A-rank.
So let's get that A-rank and switch partners!
Huh? H-Hey, doesn't that mean...
No, wait, wait. Hang on just a sec.
What?
Reaching A-rank means... you and I...
Dinner's ready.
Looks delicious.
B-But wouldn't that be kinda dangerous?
What're you getting all embarrassed about, Virgin-kun?
Even if we do things like this...
everything's totally fine!
H-H-H-H-Her breasts! Breasts! What is this soft yet firm warmth?!
I'll try my very best to be the perfect wife for you.
I'm counting on you.
W-W-Wait, please! You're really o-okay with a guy like me?
Look! It worked!
Let's keep it going!
S-S-Sorry! This is my first time doing anything like this.
I'm thirsty. I'm going to go buy something to drink.
Then I'll have a strawberry milk.
What?
We're married! You'll buy it for me, won't you?
Fine.
I just don't want any other girl to take Minami-kun away.
I have to try my hardest.
This is my first time doing all of this, too, you know...
Thank you for going along with my selfish request.
Seriously?!
I'm glad I was paired with you, Tenjin-kun.
I'm glad it was you, too, Sakurazaka-san.
So let's use first names, Shiori.
R-Right, Minami-kun.
What's with me?
I thought I didn't care if anything happened between me and Sakurazaka!
Hello! Are you gonna sit here moping forever?
Jiro
"I mean, I'm up against Tenjin Minami-kun here!"
"A killjoy virgin like me doesn't stand a chance against him!"
Don't give me a voiceover!
I'm seriously depressed here. Please just leave me alone.
Well, then...
Cheer up.
D-D-Don't make fun of people like that!
I'm not making fun of you.
Huh?
Come on. Let's actually, seriously pretend to be married.
If we reach A-rank, we'll get a happy ending.
And it'll be good practice for the real thing. What do we have to lose?
The r-real thing? I would never...
Being mopey and indecisive won't get you anywhere.
Right?
I can't help it. It's not like I've got the abundance of experience that you do.
What?!
That's got nothing to do with anything!
When you do something, you've gotta go all-in!
Do you wanna be Virgin-kun forever?
I'll get it.
Hey.
Jiro-chan, are you free? Wanna go to Aniroad?
Yeah, I'll go! Let's go now!
That's what's going on, so I'll see you later.
Hang on.
Huh?
You're leaving when we have negative points?
Well, what am I supposed to do about it?
It's obvious, isn't it?
A goodbye kiss.
Do you mean "kisu," the fish that tastes good as tempura?
What?!
I'm talking about a goodbye kiss!
Ki—
Wha?!
Jiro-chan, are you ready yet?
I guess Virgin-kun wouldn't be able to manage it.
Jiro-chan, aren't you ready yet?
You are just a virgin, after all.
Jiro! Get out here now!
I guess you'll never have that kind of relationship, so you can't help it.
You two virgins should go have fun together.
Jiro, did you die?! Or are you dead?!
Don't get mad at me later, okay?
What took you so long?
If we were at war, I'd be dead already.
Sorry.
Crap. I let her rile me up.
She was treating me like an idiot!
N-No one said anything about it being on the lips...
Jiro-kun. Jiro-kun!
Shiori?
If you don't wake up, I'll give you a kiss!
Then I'm not waking up.
Kiss me.
You really are hopeless. Honestly.
Take that, and that, and that!
What do you mean, "kiss me"?
Get up and come help me get things ready.
Huh? I-It's morning?
Crap! I fell asleep here last night?
And don't forget the reason we're acting married.
Her lips sure were soft...
No, wait! Shiori's the one I like!
Hey!
Are you still sitting there?!
I'll knock you into orbit!
Y-Yes, ma'am! Sorry!
One Week Later
As all this went on, a week passed.
Faculty Office
Excuse me.
What's this?
You had class duty today, Yakuin-kun?
The guy who does asked me to take the morning shift because he had stuff to do.
I see. Perfect timing.
Come to the faculty office with Watanabe-kun after school today.
What?
Make sure both husband and wife come.
Okay, I will.
It must be going well between Shiori and Tenjin.
I haven't been there yet.
I thought that if I acted like this, she might worry about me and say something,
Really? Then let's go. I just know you'll like it.
but she hasn't.
And just thinking that way shows how gloomy I am, right?
I'd love to go!
Okay, it's settled, then!
That back there was probably...
Hey!
What is it, Shiori?
You don't mind, do you? We're married, after all!
It's fine with me, but what about him?
You mean Jiro-kun?
It's no problem at all! He's just an old friend.
You're so cool, and you help me move forward.
My own imaginings are making me cry.
It's raining? I don't have an umbrella.
Don't worry. I have one.
I have to share an umbrella with you?
No complaining!
Man, today was just another dull day.
I had a good day, though.
My free morning gacha pull got me an S-rare card in a school swimsuit costume.
That's thanks to me, right?
Buy me something.
Can't. I started saving up for Marin-chan today.
There it is again. Hashimoto Marin.
Use honorifics for other people's girlfriends!
Marin-san.
Very good.
In the story for this event, Marin-chan makes omelet rice for you,
and it was so good!
The taste of it maxed out my love meter!
"You can't possibly know how a JPEG tastes," you say?
Fool! A JPEG is meant to be savored with the occipital lobe!
Stop for a sec.
Occipital Lobe
Parietal Lobe
Frontal Lobe
Temporal Lobe
By the way, this is the part I mean.
Move! You're in the way!
I might be late today.
Okay... Why?
I'm going to karaoke, and Minami-kun is coming!
Oh, is that so?
Later!
Wait! Wait, Watanabe.
What is it?
I just remembered. The teacher said we need to go to the faculty office.
It's about the practical.
Oh... I guess we have no choice, then.
Take care of it solo, 'kay?
Hey!
You've gotta be kidding me!
This really was the worst day ever.
To hell with that!
Your childhood friend is the pure, sweet type,
and your mock wife is a hot gyaru?!
You've got a flower in each hand!
Are you the hero of a harem anime or something?!
Oh, shut up.
I could live on the carbon dioxide Akari-chan exhales, personally.
If anything, I am carbon dioxide itself.
Huh?
Meaning no one needs me.
Faculty Office
No, it's absolutely necessary.
The marriage practical isn't playing at being friends. It's coursework.
It's necessary for graduation.
71st
Kasugahara Kyo
Sangamori Hatsune
72nd
Yakuin Jiro
Watanabe Akari
Kaizuka Yoshitake
Nakahara Miyako
Your score hasn't gone up or down for a week. It's stayed at zero.
At this rate, you really won't be able to graduate.
Talk things over with Watanabe-san so that you can strive to be a happily married couple.
Unlimited Time
Karaoke 30 minutes 100 yen Unlimited Time 1000 yen
Minami-kun, you're super good at this!
And your English is so good! I was surprised!
Thanks. But there aren't many songs I can sing.
My voice is all hoarse already.
Wanna sing together?
Of course you can!
What did you pick, Watanabe?
Go, Akari!
Oh, this is it! Higashino Kana-chan!
Here.
Huh? I don't know if I can keep singing.
I've heard you sing before. You're good.
Really?
Then maybe I'll give it my best this time.
This rain just isn't stopping.
It's easy to say to try to be a happily married couple,
but she's probably off having fun with her real love interest.
Hey, Akari is tired from singing.
Why don't we go take a little breather in the next room?
What am I thinking?!
There's no helping it.
I'll just deal with getting wet,
buy dinner from a convenience store, and head home.
Oh? You're still here at school?
Shio— Sakurazaka?! What are you doing here so late?
We had a committee meeting today.
May I sit next to you?
S-Sure.
This rain isn't letting up, huh?
Do you have an umbrella?
I forgot it!
Jiro has suffered near-fatal damage.
I-I see.
Eek!
Oh, I was mistaken.
Sorry. I thought there was a bug.
Oh, yeah, it's easy to mistake that doodle for a bug.
When I got here this morning, there was a huge one.
I thought it might've come back.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine. I was surprised, that's all.
Wait, then was that...
Bug!
Hey, Sakurazaka...
I hate that.
Huh?
It makes me feel lonely.
I want you to call me "Shiori" like you used to.
Won't you?
Wh-What's going on? What's this mean?
I don't really get it, but there's one thing I do know...
This is the time for me to be brave!
Sh-Sh-Shio—
Shiori.
Minami-kun?
But I thought you were going to be out late doing karaoke.
I remembered seeing your collapsible umbrella in the entryway.
Oh, but...
Th-That's great! I'm gonna try waiting a little longer.
You should go on ahead.
But...
I'll be fine.
See you tomorrow, Sakurazaka.
Yeah.
Here.
What sort of expression is that?
Ugh!
What's there to enjoy about sharing an umbrella with you?
And why didn't you go off somewhere with Sakurazaka-san so it'd be just the two of you?
If you had, I'd be sharing an umbrella with Minami-kun right about now.
Sorry.
Do you really have any intention of snagging that girl?
Hey!
No giving up!
For both my sake and yours.
Understand?
Yesh.
Very good.
This is probably Watanabe's way of being considerate of me.
I really am such a loser.
Is the rain starting to let up?
It might be.
Actually, I'm starving.
Should we drop by a convenience store for dinner?
No.
It's fine.
Here you go!
It's real omelet rice!
Looks delicious, doesn't it?
Y-Yeah!
Wait!
You have to move slowly, okay?
You can't let it spurt out too quickly.
Oh, not there!
Be a little more gentle...
Yes, that's so good.
Love
I filled it with my love. Please, enjoy.
I-I will, thank you!
It's good!
Of course it is!
I'll have some, too.
Wait!
Here, say "ah."
No way. I'm not doing that.
C'mon! Just go with it, please!
This is super embarrassing for me!
Damn it. I'm never doing this again.
It's delicious! That's my cooking for you!
Really? Marin-san made curry omelet rice for you?
Jiro
Thanks for the save.
Huh? What's that mean?
What was that? Why is...
What did I save you from?
...my heart pounding so fast?
I don't get it.
Jiro "Every night before taking a bath, Watanabe emerges from her room with an even sexier expression than usual. Why could that be?"
Every night before taking a bath,
Watanabe emerges from her room with an even sexier expression than usual.
Why could that be?
Jiro "The mystery was quickly solved."
The mystery was quickly solved.
Akari "Unh......... Unh......... Mmm........."
Th-That voice...
Jiro "Th......... That voice......... My body moved of its own accord, despite knowing it was wrong..."
My body moved of its own accord, despite knowing it was wrong...
Jiro "Of course that's it! I'm embarrassed at myself for imagining differently!"
Of course that's it! I'm embarrassed at myself for imagining differently!
Next time, "Imagined, but Not Real."
Imagined, but Not Real.