Why don't we go over there together?
A hotel?!
Wow!
Kamo-kun, you're pretty good with your hands!
How did you do these super detailed parts?
I just figured ladies would probably prefer Western-style castles.
She meant the beach right in front of the hotel?!
And since it had to be something easy to build with sand,
I thought about England and decided that Conwy Castle would be best.
That's a surprising talent.
You fool!
If we ever get a chance to see women's swimsuits this close again,
it'll probably only be in VR!
Well, he's got a point.
Usually, Shiori's buttons are done all the way up to the top,
but now, her chest is...
O gods, I thank you!
Jiro-kun, are you all right?
Huh? Uh, yes! What is it?
I was thinking we should make a tunnel through this castle!
We did it all the time when we were kids, remember?
We'd dig in with our hands from either side and join together in the middle.
Join together?
Okay, come on. Slide it in gently. Go slow, okay?
Okay.
Um, maybe a little deeper?
Oh! There you are, Jiro-kun!
Look at us, playing with sand. It's like we went back in time.
They're being all lovey over there. What the heck?
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
Rock, paper, scissors!
Which means Akari and Yakuin are gonna go buy stuff!
What? Me and Jiro?
We're always together. That's boring!
Well, sorry you got stuck with me.
It's pretty crowded.
It seems like it's all guy-girl pairs.
Being in a place filled with normies is getting old.
Today Couple's Discount
All items 20 yen off
It's gotta be because of this!
We should use it, too!
What? But we're not a couple!
But being married counts, doesn't it?
You turned all red! I'll assume that means you're okay with it.
"Mock"! We're mock-married!
As long as no one finds out, it's fine!
Next customer!
Let's see... Three yakisobas, and...
Couples can upgrade the size at no extra charge.
For real? That's so nice of you!
Then can we make all three of them larges?
I can't say no to a cute girlfriend like you!
You're one lucky boyfriend. I'm jealous!
Right, you're number 13. I'll call you when it's ready.
Okay.
What was with that courtesy laugh?
Do things with more style, more like a boyfriend!
Huh? What was I supposed to have done better, then?
Put your arm around my shoulders and say, "I'm proud to call her my girlfriend!"
It'd be like a dream to hear that.
Minami-kun might have done it if he were here.
That stuff doesn't just come out of nowhere.
Customer number 13!
I'll go get it.
What was that? He's so infuriating!
Hey, you alone?
Oh, crap. Where were we a minute ago?
Does Akari know him?
I can't tell!
Jiro, over here!
What? You were waiting for a guy?
You're two totally different types. That's hilarious!
Um, are you acquaintances of hers?
Ding, ding, ding! Acquaintances! We just became acquainted!
You know they're not! They're hitting on me!
Yeah, of course...
Hey, bro, you're here with her, right?
Will you tell us her name?
We've asked, but she won't tell us.
Hey, are you staying somewhere around here tonight? Is it close?
U-Um, would you mind letting her go? She doesn't like what you're doing.
Oh, here it comes!
You after this girl, too?
No, um...
She's a little intense for you, ain't she, bro?
You look like a virgin, though. Are you?
Sh-She's my wife.
What?!
She's married?!
Sorry, bro!
Yeah, uh... Be happy together!
L-Listen, Jiro...
I'm sorry!
Huh?
I couldn't think up a lie on the spot,
and I figured you must've hated being called my wife...
B-But calling you my girlfriend would've been... you know...
You are seriously infuriating!
I said I'm sorry!
I never said I hated it!
Huh?
I-I didn't say that, did I?
Don't just assume things like that.
Y-You were so cool... and then you ruined it, you idiot.
If you're always like that, you'll never get a girlfriend!
Don't apologize for everything.
I feel like a loser for letting my heart race.
And in the practical, too...
Show me you're man enough to use me for practice.
F-For practice?
You get it now? Okay, so let's head back!
Wh-Wha...
Hey! Quit pushing!
They're gonna tease us for taking so long because of you.
It wasn't my fault!
Walk faster!
I can't deal with that kind of thing...
This is paradise.
Don't talk like an old man.
This is so nostalgic. It feels like a school trip.
Mei-chan, you're not sunburned, are you?
No, I rubbed some oil on, so I'm fine.
But I guess a day isn't enough to even out a tan.
Oh, the tan lines around here are fading, though.
Y-You've tanned some, too!
You're right! And I put on sunblock and everything.
Come on, let's hurry up and get in.
So then I asked him,
"And how many kilos do you think you've gained since we started dating?"
It's impossible to stay the "perfect girl" 24 hours a day, right?
That's so not okay.
You're working hard to stay beautiful, and he just doesn't get it.
Bet he'll never get married.
Yeah, for real.
We can hear them talking.
Anyway, since we're on the subject, how's it going at your place, Akari?
Indeed.
My place?
That virgin seems like he'd have unrealistic dreams about girls.
She complained about him all the time at first.
And you thought there was no way it could last this long.
Th-That's because he's super, uber sloppy!
So he's sloppy at home...
Doesn't Virgin-kun actually treat you better since he's got so little experience?
In the end, it's all about kindness, right?
If he isn't kind, it won't feel good anyway.
Like my ex before my last ex...
Before we'd do it, I seriously thought about reading my mental notes aloud to him.
Hey, um...
We can hear everything you're saying. You okay with that?
It's totally fine! Actually, Hamano-san, you should join in!
You, too, Sakurazaka-san!
Huh?
How do your relationship chats usually go?
I... I, um...
After hearing what you said, I think it's all about caring for someone.
It's sort of a way to give yourself the feeling that you really like them,
and I'd like to believe the other party wants to feel seen, too.
It's not about being good or bad at it.
It's wanting to make eye contact even one more time.
I think I like that kind of thing.
Well said!
That's it, exactly!
I want to really feel that I'm loved.
Hamano-san, will you marry me?
Why are you clinging to me like that?
C'mon, cut it out!
Sorry for talking about this right now.
Huh? Oh, no, it's fine. I'm the one who should apologize.
I, um... I don't have much experience, so I couldn't join the conversation, that's all.
Really? But you're super cute!
But I get it. It's hard to jump into a conversation like that.
When it comes to the stuff they were talking about, I'm no match for those two.
I-It's very educational.
You're so serious!
If it were Jiro-kun...
If it was Jiro...
Akari!
We're gonna head back first.
Okay.
Women
Men
Was the men's bath pretty big?
Uh... yeah, kinda.
O-Oh, cool.
Hey, you got burned.
I know, right?
The shower hurt like hell. Especially the back of my neck.
Hang on a sec. I should have...
Come here. I'll put it on for you.
Huh?
Wow, it's really noticeable!
U-Um, don't you need to get back to your room?
What's that supposed to mean? Do you want me to leave?
No, just...
It might look weird if we're together too long.
They might start teasing us.
You worry too much.
Wait, so your neck isn't ticklish, huh?
I guess not. I never really had any ticklish spots.
Then how about here?
Whoa! It's not ticklish? For real?
Get off me! What if someone sees us?
We haven't done this yet today.
W-We're not doing the practical right now...
But ever since we got here, there's been this distance between us.
It makes me feel weird.
Please... just be the way you always...
Akari!
Oh.
Were you in the middle of something?
Nope! I was just telling Jiro he should treat me to a drink.
I think I'll have apple juice.
Hey! I never said I'd buy you anything!
Oh, really? I'll have a cola.
Would you look at this? Seriously, I am so done with him.
So, Takamiya-san... You wanted a cola, right?
Yeah. Thanks!
Aka—Watanabe, what did you say you wanted?
Watanabe...
Apple juice.
Right.
Thanks!
So, he's like a major no, right?
Uh-oh. I stepped on some kind of land mine.
I hope nothing bad happens...
Watanabe Akari
Time starts now
10 minutes
The beach shop
You will come.
Yes, I will.
Hey, where's Akari?
She said she was going to the convenience store.
What? But I thought we were going to play cards.
Do you know where Jiro-chan is?
He said he was going to go wander around.
What? Are any shops still open?
At this hour, probably just the convenience store.
Sheesh...
Shall we? For a change of pace.
Um, I'm very sorry.
There it is.
You don't know why I'm angry, but you start off with an apology anyway. Like always.
Yes. I don't know why you're angry.
I'm very sorry.
I'm telling you not to apologize when you don't know the reason for it!
Are you stupid?!
Y-Yes!
I'm sor—Okay!
Whoa, what?! What are you...
That swimsuit...
I've been looking forward to it.
I got to come to the ocean with you, even if it's for work.
So she meant what she said?
But you just keep worrying about how other people see us.
When I do talk to you, you're cold toward me.
It's like I'm the only one excited about this.
I hate it so much.
She hates it? But that...
That makes it sound like she's jealous.
No, it's nothing, really.
Am I stupid? I can't get the wrong idea.
It's just her usual "I hate it" syndrome.
Anyway!
I know you don't want people to see you with me, but...
No! It's not that!
Yes, it is!
I'm telling you, it's not!
It's the other way around.
Being around a plain, boring guy like me is just embarrassing for you, isn't it?
Huh? Why should that matter?
Who I hang out with is up to me.
People like me worry about that kind of thing!
Even if you're okay with it, other people might think things.
And it's not like we have to spend time together right now—
Why do you have to say sad things like that?
Look at me more, like you do when we're at home.
Come on... Look.
Look! Look!
When we're at home, all you do is stare at my chest, you moron!
Ow, ow, ow!
I already know about all that, so don't try to act cool when we're out here!
The pressure! All kinds of pressure!
Calm down, Akari!
Just let go for a minute! Okay?
You won't get your message across this way.
Come on. Look me in the eye and talk to me.
Yeah... Okay.
I'm glad she's so docile today.
I hate that we're not a married couple when we're outside the house.
I hate you acting cold and calling me by my last name.
When I see you talking with those other girls all the time...
It's like you're not my husband anymore.
I can't help thinking,
what if even after we're back home, we aren't a married couple anymore?
And I hate feeling like that!
Um, is it okay for me to ask what you mean by that?
What do you mean, "what do I mean"? I don't get it.
Well, like... How do I put it...
You want to be together even when we're out,
y-you want me to call you by your first name,
and you hate it when I talk to other girls... right?
It's like...
I can't help thinking that... those are things a jealous girlfriend might say.
Wait, what? For real?
Y-You're not making sense!
What do you mean, "for real"?
Well, I mean...
Jealous? Like hell I am!
M-More like I'm angry because you act like I'm just a convenience!
That's what she meant?!
For now, I'll make sure to call you by your first name.
You should've just said that from the start.
Wow! The moon's beautiful tonight!
It's brighter than I thought it'd be.
The breeze feels so nice!
Oh, by the way, I was watching a drama on TV yesterday,
and there was a girl who looked like you.
Oh, the one playing the younger sister?
Yeah! Do you get compared to her a lot?
What do I do now?
It's too cramped in here. Scoot over that way!
You're the one who dragged me in here!
Shh!
This sucks. I just want to get out of here already.
How is complaining gonna help?
Right now, we just have to make sure Shiori and Hamano don't see us.
That's always where you end up.
Did you say something?
Nope, nothing.
It took a lot to wear this swimsuit...
But even when we're this close,
in Jiro's heart, I don't even exist.
Back when all I did was chase after Minami-kun, I managed to be a lot more optimistic.
But now, every time it feels fun or reassuring to have Jiro beside me,
I get scared that he'll leave.
Even right now,
I can feel that Jiro really cares for Sakurazaka-san.
It's something I've known about since we first met,
but I still feel all muddled.
I really hate this.
Akari? Are you feeling sick?
Really? That's a relief.
It's hot, but can you hang in there just a little longer?
If I do, what then?
What do you mean?
You'll be able to leave?
Do you hear someone talking?
S-Stop that! Don't scare me!
You really can't stand that kind of thing, huh?
What if there's...
a ghost or something over there?
Mei-chan!
Huh? There's no one here.
Sorry about that. My mistake.
Thank goodness.
Maybe what I heard came from the road...
Safe!
Ow!
Hey, are you nuts?!
Quit banging around!
Mei-chan, let's go back now!
Hurry! Hurry!
Wait...
This seriously sucks.
Come on, get off of me already.
I can't believe you'd ogle my chest in an emergency like this.
That's so wrong.
I swear, that's how all guys are.
I regret wearing this swimsuit.
You wanted me to look, didn't you?
Th-That was just... something I said in the moment.
And you need to hurry up and forget that!
Oh, I get it.
So you were just toying with me, is that it?
No, it's not—
Yes, it is.
Wanting me to use your first name in public, getting mad at me earlier...
If you just said all that "in the moment,"
then I'm not gonna change a thing.
I hate you, Jiro.
I hate this. I'm so embarrassed. I'm gonna die.
Hey, what's wrong? It's too hot for this.
Come on, it's all clear. We can get out of here now.
And your knee is poking me. Can you move it?
That's... not my knee.
Wh-What?
I'm serious.
You're kidding...
Sorry.
Raise your face up.
Hey, Jiro...
Did looking at me make that happen?
What? W-Wait!
W-We can't! We can't!
Jiro, we can't! Th-There's an order to these kinds of things!
Huh?
Jiro?!
They said it's mild heatstroke. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hey, so...
Sorry. I heard that you went and got people to carry me.
Also, um... sorry about all that other stuff, too.
Didn't I tell you not to apologize?
It makes me feel worse.
I'm telling you not to apologize!
And also!
"You wanted me to look, didn't you?" What was with that tone?
It's unbelievable!
All those times you stole glances at home?
I was letting you look because I felt sorry for you!
You should be grateful to me, idiot!
You're too loud! Keep it down!
Instead of just that kind of stuff,
I want you to look at all the different parts of me.
We've already been married for four months,
but I don't know anything about you yet.
I-I mean, knowing about each other will make living together more fun, right?
I want to see and know all the different parts of you, too.
Since we're still married and all.
Okay?
Sure.
As I looked at Akari smiling and saying, "It's already been four months,"
I thought a lot of different things...
But something about the way she said "still" stuck in an odd spot and stayed that way.
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
Knock, knock! Let's play cards!
Let's do it!
You can come in!
Old Maid? Sevens? Whoever loses gets a penalty!
Okay!
This face pack feels great!
Right?
Next Time
More Than a Confession, but Not Yet a Broken Heart.
Next time, "More Than a Confession, but Not Yet a Broken Heart."