I'm sorry, gods!
The person on my mind has changed since last time,
so I've come to ask again.
My chances may be really low, but...
Kinda feels like something scandalous happened while those two were all alone.
But I'll do everything I can!
And so I ask for your favor!
It's hopeless.
It's popped up in my memory every day since then.
If Akari-chan isn't special to you,
then will you show me...
a part of you that
Akari-chan doesn't know?
Why did I do that?
I'm so glad summer break started right after that!
I panicked. I know that.
My first was you...
but was it different for you?
Um... Well, I mean...
Before that kiss with me in the nurse's office, Jiro-kun had already...
I didn't want to know...
But it's easy to tell.
Jiro-kun's wife is Akari-chan...
So does that mean I'm just his childhood friend?
That's awful. It's like I'm someone he had an affair with.
Jiro-kun...
What were you feeling when you kissed me?
I...
Jiro-kun...
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
Crap. What am I supposed to do?
Now that it's come to this...
Chloris
there's only one thing to do.
Take this!
Huh? What is that?
Chloris
I'm sorry.
Wha?!
Chloris has kissed the Hero.
I'm so sorry!
Once we grow up, being childhood friends won't be enough to keep me by your side.
Is it that moment with Shiori again?
In that moment, Shiori kissed me...
And it didn't seem like she hated it.
To be honest, I felt like it was the only chance I'd get...
Like the first love I'd half given up on might bloom in that moment.
But afterward, Shiori apologized over and over,
and then she only said, "Let's head back."
What was she feeling?
Why did she kiss me and then apologize?
And anyway, that kind of thing...
First you fall in love and confess, then you start going out, hold hands...
Shouldn't it come after all that?
What did she mean when she said being childhood friends wasn't enough to stay close?
What am I supposed to do?
If I had more EXP built up, I'd probably be able to come up with an answer, but...
No matter how much I think about it, I have no idea!
I think I'll go buy some cola, potato chips, and manga for now.
Jiro has run away.
Young Ace
An Ideal Life as a Sponging Boyfriend
Special Bonus Item 2
Bungo Stray Dogs Special Clear File Folder
This manga is already out?
Oh, excuse me!
I'm sorry!
What?!
I-I never thought we'd meet in a place like this.
Y-Yes, indeed.
Why are you being so formal?
I was just so surprised...
Wait, so... you read manga?
No, I went to the shop next door to buy notebooks,
and my little brother asked me to get this.
Little brother... You mean Kenta?
Yeah. He's been wanting to see you.
What? He remembers me?
Yeah. Since I've mentioned you, he's been wondering about you.
You... talk about me?
Oh, it looks like this is the last copy.
Here, you take it.
Huh? I couldn't!
It's okay. I was gonna go shopping after this, anyway.
You can buy it and take it home.
You really are kind.
Huh? Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Thank you.
What a relief!
It was probably better to talk like this today
than starting out the new term with things still awkward.
Whoa, are you serious?
I think it's just a passing summer shower, but...
I didn't think it would rain.
You don't have an umbrella?
No. Maybe I'll buy one somewhere nearby.
"Well, I'll see you next term." Is that what I say now?
Is this where this event ends?
Isn't this actually a chance to cement some future plans?
But then again...
Oh, come on! Say something, me!
Um, do you want to come to my place?
The one at the training dorm?
Huh?
It's nearby.
And I'd like to talk some more until the rain lets up.
What do you think?
Are you sure?
S-Since this was so sudden, I don't have anything prepared,
but since I got the chance to see you...
Only if you have time, though.
Th-Thank you for inviting me over.
Hang on just a minute.
I want to make sure it isn't too messy.
My hands are sweating like crazy!
I hope I don't smell sweaty...
Welcome home, darling.
Huh?
J-Just kidding!
Sorry for doing that out of nowhere. Well, please, come on in!
Th-Thank you for having me.
The place is pretty stark, isn't it?
There's nothing at all in here.
My place is the same way!
And all the furniture's the same, so I kinda feel at home.
May I sit next to you?
O-Of course! It's your place, after all.
It smells amazing.
What?!
Is this, y'know, quality stuff?
Oh, uh... Y-Yes, it's pretty much the real deal.
Wow, really?
Just what I'd expect from you!
Of course he meant the coffee!
I'm such an idiot!
I am way too happy right now!
I haven't taken in a single word of this manga,
but I don't even care!
Her outfit is so demure...
She's so cute!
Her skin is so pale, and her wrists are so slender.
And she smells nice.
She's slim and dainty, but she seems soft, too.
And her eyelashes are so long...
Um... Does something about me look weird?
N-No... I was just wondering what you're reading.
Oh, this? It's a novel called Hello Summer, Goodbye.
It's really good. I'll lend it to you sometime.
Th-Thanks.
I-I'm just going to go...
S-Sure.
When our eyes met, I didn't know what to do.
Maybe it was too pushy of me to invite him over after all.
Was he bored?
Or maybe he couldn't bring himself to say he wanted to leave?
What if he hates me now?
Does she hate me now?
Is she fed up because I don't know how to take the lead?
But I mean... It's just...
I'm alone in a room with a girl who kissed me!
It'd be impossible not to be overly conscious of her!
Shiori isn't the type to be that assertive with just anyone.
So the fact that she kissed me...
I'm allowed to be a little happy about that, right?
Maybe we do need to have a good talk about what happened that day...
Jiro-kun!
Yes?
Look outside!
Huh?
Whoa!
It's a double rainbow!
That's so cool!
I've never seen anything like it before! It's beautiful!
Oh, I know!
I'll get a shot with the rainbow. You get in it, too!
Huh? Y-You sure?
Okay! I'm taking it!
It looks great!
Double rainbows bring happiness.
I hope something nice happens.
Could you send that to me, too?
Of course!
Thanks.
Let's see...
Is it... now?
If I'm going to take a step, is now the time?
Um, I...
Look. You're in this one, too!
I'll send it at the same time.
It's the one we took at the beach. I really love this photo.
Everyone looks so happy.
Oh, right. Were you about to say something?
Huh? Oh...
Uh, never mind. I forgot what it was.
The beach was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah!
I've been running from romance and that kind of thing all this time.
Which feeling is friendship?
Where does love start?
They're my own feelings, but at some point, I couldn't understand them anymore.
Why did I decide not to say anything in that moment?
Getting to a good place with Shiori was my dream, and yet...
It's probably just Kamo.
Sorry, but I'm in no mood to deal with you.
Oh, for crying out loud, what do you want?!
Message Just Now Watanabe Akari sent a sticker. 7 more messages
Akari?!
P O P
Jiro
That was a shock.
It's been half a month...
Yes, what is it?
Jiro
I'm bored
My heart!
No! Don't give me that, heart!
I bet she's sent that to a bunch of people.
Yes, what is it?
Jiro
I'm bored
So am I
Ugh, I hate this!
Why am I so nervous?
It's just Jiro!
Then we'll meet in front of Seishun Station in 2 hours!
It's a date♥︎
What?!
During summer break? Me and Akari?
Points for the practical aren't being counted right now!
There's nothing in it for her, right?
What kind of trap is this?
Up until now, the two of us have only ever gone out to do regular errands, like shopping!
That way next!
She's not gonna make me buy her a ton of clothes, is she?
Virgin-kun, you seriously came here?
Or maybe it's not even that! She might just be messing with me!
That's hilarious! It was just a joke!
Sorry! I didn't think you'd take me seriously.
That's it! That's gotta be it!
It's a date♥︎
But supposing she's actually serious,
and she really is inviting me out, just as friends, of course...
Should I decline?
I just told her I was bored, though.
I don't have anything I can wear to walk around with a gyaru!
Ten minutes early, huh?
A plain white T-shirt should be a safe choice, right?
I saw that written on an aggregator site, so...
Seriously, is someone out there waiting or something?
And is Akari really going to come?
It's nearly time.
Jeez, she didn't even show up.
I mean, I knew it was coming, but...
15 minutes later
Guess I'll go home.
Jiro!
I'm so glad you're still here!
It took longer than I thought to get ready.
I ran out in a rush.
Then, after I got to the station, I realized I'd forgotten my phone.
I'm super sorry!
Jiro, are you angry?
Huh? Uh, no, I'm not.
I didn't think you'd really come, anyway.
What?!
What does that mean?
S-Sorry!
Um, it's just that we don't usually do stuff like this with just us two,
so I guess I just couldn't imagine it.
But... I told you it was a date, didn't I?
After all the effort I put in to get ready, there's no way I wouldn't show up.
Hey...
Do I look cute?
You have nothing to say?
I-It's not like the stuff you usually wear, so it's new and different!
And?
Um, I think clothes like the ones you're wearing today... are really nice.
Thanks. That makes me really happy.
Because this outfit is just for you.
Huh?
You said before that you liked things like this, right?
So... It's not the kind of thing I'd normally wear,
so buying it was a first for me.
What?
Huh? Why?
She wanted it to suit my tastes?
Huh?
Okay, let's go!
I have a ton of places I wanna go today!
Come with me to all of them, okay?
Wha... What is even going on here?!
Which one should I get?
Have you decided what you're getting?
No... I don't even know which way is up right now.
Then you should get this one.
I seriously have no idea.
Why is Akari doing this with me?
I bet you didn't know about this café, right?
I'd heard of it. We saw it on TV together.
You said it was a favorite of yours.
You remembered.
And now it's your momentous Ex-choco debut.
Drink up! Hurry!
Like it?
Yeah! Even more than I imagined!
Really? But isn't it bitter?
There is some bitterness, but it's good.
Let me taste it!
Huh?
I can't? You're so stingy.
Go ahead.
Ugh! You liar! It's super bitter!
I know that face.
You're thinking, "That was an indirect kiss," aren't you?
No... er, yes, I am.
Jeez, stop getting all embarrassed over stuff like that.
It makes me feel embarrassed, too.
Huh?
Has Akari always been like this?
They're so cute!
Oh, wow! They really are just lying around everywhere!
They're just too cute!
They really are used to this! How cute!
I'm used to seeing Akari smile like this now,
There, there.
but I never would've imagined it based on my first impression of her.
If we hadn't been a married couple,
I'd probably never have known this side of her.
Here?
You're such a good kitty.
Oh, it's so cute!
That's all you've said since we got here.
Yeah, because my dearest wish has come true!
Here, Jiro! Try petting it!
It's really soft!
See?
You're right!
Meow.
Playing games through the night every day is the real thrill of summer break,
but it might be okay to have days like this sometimes, too.
That's what I found myself thinking.
I'll send you that picture in the chat, okay?
Sure. Thanks.
Oh! I'll send this, too.
A picture from the cat café.
Ack! When did someone take that?
The lady said, "I'm taking your picture now."
I didn't notice at all.
Plus, this picture looks sort of like...
a family photo, doesn't it?
Huh?
I mean, it might be because of the way it was taken, but...
It's like the cat is the baby, and...
I-I-I was just thinking that some family photos look like that, is all!
She must be so creeped out!
That's hilarious! What the heck?
Huh? She isn't creeped out?
It'd be nice if we could keep it as a pet during our practical.
I guess... it would.
Let's go to the cat café together again. I'll invite you.
Pedestrian Crossing Signal
Could it be that she invited me because she actually wanted to hang out with me?
You said yours is the upstairs ticket gate, right?
That's right. What about you?
I'm taking the subway.
What? Oh, sorry! We already passed that!
Don't be! It's really close.
This kinda feels weird, doesn't it?
We usually go home to the same place,
but this time we're saying goodbye and going to different places.
Yeah.
But... that's going to happen eventually, isn't it?
I might feel a little lonely.
Just kidding! Oh!
Huh?
I forgot to buy a charm at the shrine!
A charm? What kind?
I-I'll tell you later!
Huh? Hey, Akari!
Hey, wait up! Akari!
Jiro-kun? And Watanabe-san, too?
Shiori?
Sakurazaka-san?
What a coincidence. Were you shopping?
You're carrying a lot.
Yeah. You two, too?
That's right. I figured he'd be holed up in his room without me around,
so I thought I'd get him a little sunlight.
I see. Are you on your way home now?
Yeah. I just have something to do at the shrine.
Watanabe-san, do you remember that we met at the shrine in the spring?
Oh, yeah.
I was just about to go pay my respects there.
Can I go, too? Want to race?
Huh? What? Race?
Sure. Let's do it! No holding back!
What?!
Okay, then, Jiro...
Huh? Wai—
Would you?
Hang on! Hey!
Ready...
Go!
Here!
Got it!
Watanabe-san, you're really fast!
You're not bad yourself, Sakurazaka-san!
Oh, my. What's happened here?
Are you girls all right?
I'm sorry we worried you. We were just racing each other, that's all.
Oh, is that so? You gave us a fright.
Didn't they, Jiro-san?
Yes, they did.
Jiro?
Come, now. If you don't pay attention, you'll trip and fall.
Right.
Honestly...
He does seem a little like Jiro.
Come on.
He really does.
I have no idea what's going on.
Now, really put your hearts into it!
Right!
This place is famous for fulfilling romantic wishes, isn't it?
I...
Thanks! I'll handle the rest myself.
Okay, thanks.
Akari! I'll help make dinner!
Jiro has leveled up! He has gone with Lancia and Chloris to face their next adventure.
This looks tasty!
Right?
What're you writing with the ketchup tonight?
Love
Hmm, what shall I write?
Huh?
Let's see...
Oh!
Hang on a sec.
This is...
Go like this, and then like this...
And it's done!
Ack!
Your special omelet rice.
2nd
Miyajidake Asahi Najima Nanako
3rd
Tenjin Minami Sakurazaka Shiori
4th
Yakuin Jiro Watanabe Akari
Okubo Osamu Shuto Kyoko
Are you serious?