Here I go!
What?!
Sachi, you're B-rank?
That's amazing.
He just takes it so seriously, you know?
You doing what needs doing?
Don't be dumb.
We each have partners of our own, so we're over all that.
And if we make A-rank, we'll change partners, anyway.
No way!
I couldn't take it!
I'd be so depressed if Ryou-kun were here at this school!
If Ryou-kun made it to A-rank and lived with lots of different girls,
I'd never be able to stand it!
There's NegaNatsu again.
You love Ryou-kun way too much.
It's not that easy to get to A-rank.
It's rough enough just sharing a room with a total stranger,
but you have to pretend to be married, too.
But, I mean...
Ryou-kun is just so hot!
Keep it down, you lot!
Watch the game!
Yes, sir.
Over here! Cover!
Are you staring at Sakurazaka-san again,
Jiro-chan?
Shut up.
Wow!
Now that's an ikemen.
It's like he's completely different from us on a biological level.
By the way, did you hear the rumor about Sakurazaka-san?
A rumor?
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
What's this rumor about Minami-kun?
It's still a breaking story, but...
They say Tenjin isn't going to swap partners.
What?
I heard that, too.
Even though everyone who reaches A-rank switches partners, right?
And they get to keep the points from the previous pairing just as they are, too.
But this practical is supposed to be preparing us for the future,
so the school probably wants us to try various combinations.
But...
I don't like that.
It feels like picking out and dropping spouses over and over.
You know it isn't like that at all, Akari.
At this rate, it might really be possible...
for those two...
Everything's fine. It's still only the first month.
Akari, will you marry me?
No fair!
I want in on this, too! Come on!
Come on!
Just give it a rest already!
You're the one who needs to give it a rest!
What? I want in on this, too! Come on!
Hey, Jiro-chan.
Don't get so down about this.
Being the wife of an ikemen like Tenjin instead of you
is better for Sakurazaka-san, too!
Whose side are you on?
That's obvious, isn't it?
Sakurazaka-san's.
Nay, I am an ally of all women!
Hooray for the hero! Hooray!
He's so cool!
He's amazing!
It's just too unfair.
Hey, Jiro-chan! Lookie, lookie! What d'you think, huh? How's it look?
When I said that, we gained points.
What? For real?
Jiro-kun!
Shiori?
It's hot today, isn't it?
Yeah.
Jiro-kun?
You seem kind of down. Is it about the practical?
Huh?
Oh, you fought with Watanabe-san again, didn't you?
It's not like that.
Really? I'm glad.
Watanabe-san is a good girl, so don't cause too much trouble for her.
If I told her right now that she's the reason I'm stressing...
What face would she make?
Thanks. It was a request from Minami-kun.
Jiro-kun?
Hey, Shiori...
Are you going to stay...
by Tenjin's side forever?
Ugh! This is seriously unbelievable!
Why just me? All of us were talking.
And these are so dusty!
Watanabe?
Huh?
Huh? M-Mina— Why?!
That was close.
Sorry. I shouldn't have just talked to you out of nowhere.
Th-Thanks for saving me. I'm fine now.
Sure thing.
Wh-Why are you here, anyway?
They asked me to put away the balls.
Oh... I see.
What do I do? My heart's pounding.
He'll hear it.
I'm really sorry about that.
You're not hurt, are you?
No.
That's a relief...
Minami-kun still makes my heart race.
Huh? A relief?
Why?
Let's get this cleanup over with.
At this rate, it might really be possible...
for those two...
Mi...
Minami-kun!
Um... are...
A-Are you going to...
stay with Sakurazaka-san... forever?
I might.
If she says she's all right with that, then I might.
Things are going well right now.
Oh.
So I do love him after all.
Watanabe?
S-Sorry!
It's just so dusty in here.
I think I might've gotten something in my eye.
M-Minami-kun?
Watanabe.
Look me in the eyes.
Jiro-chan!
Sheesh.
I asked him to help me close all the windows.
Aha.
Jiro—
...chaaaan...
Um...
I dunno.
Switching partners isn't something I can decide on my own.
O-Oh, right! Yeah, you're right.
Sorry for asking such a dumb question.
A-And Tenjin's pretty amazing, right?
But...
But if you made it up to A-rank,
then I...
Never mind!
We need to get changed before the next class starts!
Shiori!
I'll make it to A-rank!
And when that happens...
If you're A-rank, too...
then...
Shiori...
C-Can you and I—
Jiro-chan!
This is huge!
As huge as if you bought packs in bulk and all the cards inside were secret ones!
Listen to me!
I'm begging you. Leave right now.
If you don't, I will very likely send you to your grave.
As a living sacrifice?!
Jiro-kun?
Kamo, kamo...
Sorry about that.
It's nothing. Never mind.
I see.
Wait, were you in the middle of something here, too?
That's right. And what do you mean by "here, too"?
Well, I just saw Tenjin and Akari-chan over there—
What about us?
Huh?
What're you guys talking about?
N-Nothing!
Huh? Why...
What is this atmosphere?
Huh? What battlefield is this?
Preview
I'm trapped by an accident that wasn't my fault!
Escape
Intervention
Friendship
Quick Joke
The only action left to me is to summon...
a monster!
Attack 9999 Defense 0001
Come!
Strongest of All Quick Jokes!
Oh, hang on. There are girls here.
I'll get majorly burned, and that'll be the end of my high school life.
Normies
Next time, "I Die Inside."
Next Time
I Die Inside
Kamo Sadaharu, standing by!
Come to think of it, has anyone called me by name in this anime?
Oh, Kamo. I've been looking for you.
Oh, sorry. Your name is Kamo, isn't it?
It is. It's Kamo Sadaharu.
Here. The key to the storage room.
The teacher said to give it to you. You're on the PE committee, right?
Oh. Yes, that's right.
All yours,
Kamo.
My heart.
Oh, right.
Shiori, did you turn in the form to continue our marriage practical?
No, not yet.
I forgot, too.
Then should we go together at lunch?
It's due today, right?
Yeah. Where do we have to go again?
Jiro-kun, we're going on ahead, okay?
S-Sure.
I've got work today, so...
So you won't need dinner, right?
Oh, that's right. I wanted to ask you...
W-Well, I guess I'll go return the key.
Oh, dear. What kind of face is that?
Whatever it is, good luck, my friend.
Listen, Watanabe...
We should get back.
We'll be late for class.
Right.
Huh? Where's Akari?
She left early.
She said we can just say it's a cold and leave it at that.
What? That's hilarious.
She went home?
Lancia
You love Chloris, don't you? Why don't you just hurry up and go to her?!
Leave Lancia here and go see Chloris. It's no good. You just can't leave Lancia on her own.
Wander, wander.
Kamo
Wander, wander, wander.
Kamo is wandering nearby, as though he wants to tell Jiro something.
Wander, wander, wander, wander, wander.
Kamo
Leave Lancia here and go see Chloris. It's no good. You just can't leave Lancia on her own.
Ack!
Loom.
What are you doing?
Well...
I was just thinking, "Huh, Tenjin's still here."
Man, what is it with all this "Tenjin," "Tenjin," "Tenjin"?
Just spit it out already!
Well...
Should I really say it, though?
I mean, Tenjin was nice enough to remember my name.
And he kinda smelled nice.
I remember your name, too!
Kamo, Kamo, Kamo, Kamo, Kamo—
What white-fleshed fish tastes great as tempura?
Huh?
K-Kissing happened.
Huh? With you?
Ha. Me? When even my family's pet cat bites me?
S-Sorry.
Between Akari-chan and Tenjin!
I happened to see it!
I don't know what led up to it, or what their relationship is, though.
Akari-chan seemed embarrassed.
So I'm certain of it. That was—
And?
Huh?
If it's true, then what?
But, I mean... you...
Well, I guess you're right.
Even if it's true, it's got nothing to do with you.
I see.
With Tenjin-sama, huh?
I'm happy for you. Congratulations, Watanabe.
Lancia
I'm not even Team Lancia, am I?
Today, we're going to limit ourselves to affordable cosmetics.
I'm back.
These days, there are lots of really amazing low-priced products.
First, there's this primer that I've been super hooked on lately.
I heard you have a cold.
It's great for toning, and it has lavender undertones.
I tend to have my hair black, so using a primer with purple tones...
Oh, that's right! Speaking of hair...
Ta-da! Nuanced Fancy Water for...
Do you have a fever?
This lip balm has beautifying essences in it! It's godly!
I'm seriously buying it on repeat!
I recommend number 7 for people with blue tones to their skin!
It's a tinted balm, so it'll last even through a kiss!
I'm so sorry that I'm not Tenjin.
If you have occasion to, that is!
What?
Why are you suddenly bringing up Minami-kun?
Well?
Oh, uh...
What?
It's nothi—
Tell me.
Uh...
You and Tenjin apparently got a lot closer during PE. I heard about it.
I was happy for you.
Happy? Why now, though?
Yeah, I was happy that I got to talk to him, but...
So if you're happy, you'll kiss someone?
Huh? I don't know what you're talking about.
There's no need to hide it.
It's amazing that you could embrace like that in the storeroom.
If you and Tenjin are gonna end up together,
I'm gonna cheer you on.
It's cause for celebration.
Wait, that's—
No... Yeah.
It's cause for celebration.
Oh, man! This is hilarious!
Huh?
That must've been when I had him check my eye for dust!
That misunderstanding is, like, straight out of a manga!
I will send him to his grave!
██████████████████████████████████
I will send him to his grave!!
KILL
And anyway, that kind of thing doesn't just happen out of the blue, right?
I'm actually hurt right now because he's not switching partners.
Why would you even believe that? Sad!
Because... I know how hard you're trying.
I told you...
I'm working hard because he just won't look my way.
Well, yeah, but...
I mean, you're giving it all you've got.
Why shouldn't it pay off a little?
What an idiot.
It's super...
hilarious...
Watanabe!
Hey! What are you looking at?
Let go...
You idiot...
Don't!
Look away!
I-I looked away!
I can't see anything now!
I panicked and ended up doing that.
I don't know what the right thing to do is!
I'm not the kind of guy who encounters women crying all that often!
Before, Watanabe was sleeping, so I was safe,
but this time I have no excuse!
Of course she'd hate being held like that
by a guy she doesn't love!
Jiro, the bath is free.
Mine aren't dry, so I borrowed this.
Huh? Borrowed what?
Your shirt.
Whoa! Are you serious?!
The "boyfriend shirt" thing hits this hard?!
Vanilla & Chocolate Bar
And she's getting super close!
What changed all of a sudden? There's usually a longer break!
Doing this after what just happened...
is gonna make me remember the physical sensations!
L-Look, I know you're probably like this because it's just me, but be more careful.
I don't exactly know where to look.
Is your heart racing, Repressed-kun?
No! I'm used to seeing stuff like this now.
Day after day...
Liar.
I can feel it right here, pounding really hard.
Jiro?
Earthly Desires Begone!!!!!!!
Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly desires begone Earthly... desires... begone...
Trophy Earned. Happy New Year!
I think I'll succumb before I ring it 108 times.
Huh?
Jiro, you're so weird.
Don't make fun of me.
You should only dress like that for Tenjin.
You jealous?
You're kind of adorable, Jiro!
You know, dressed like that, you really will catch a cold!
Jiro, you believed that I kissed him, right?
I'm not that easy, you know.
I-I said I was sorry about that.
You think I've gone around and kissed all kinds of people.
That's not what I—
Smooch.
It's just you, Jiro.
That was my first, so yours is the only kiss I know.
Seriously, you're such an idiot!
S-Suddenly kissing me on the mouth like that...
Those were some serious "I'm a virgin" vibes!
You went in too hard, and you were lousy at it!
Having that as my first kiss is just wrong!
What was that, anyway?
That was really and truly my first kiss!
Are you even listening?
Hey, are you alive?
Lancia
Why'd you come back? Idiot.
Hey! Jiro!
Jiro: "Don't get the wrong idea, me! She just ended up paired with me, and it just happened to be her first..."
Jiro, are you listening?
Hey, Jiro, I'm talking to you!
Ugh, hello?! Jiro, Jiro, Jiro, Jiro, Jiro!
Jiro: "And it's totally possible that it could have been some other guy..."
I'm the only one who knows.
Jiro: "I said, don't get the wrong idea here! This is just a practical..."
Jiro:  "That's all it is!"
Oh, God. I'm super happy.
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
Did you think it was over?
Too bad!
My battle phase hasn't ended yet!
Escape
Intervention
Friendship
Quick Joke
It's my turn!
Intervention
Effect, activate!
Intervention!
Everyone, please don't fight because of me!
I'm so glad I didn't do that!
Next Time
More Than a Nosebleed, but Less Than a Kiss.
Next time, "More Than a Nosebleed, but Less Than a Kiss."
Kissing again?!