Watanabe!
I have class duties today, so I'm gonna get going.
Is this all the recycling we have to put out today?
That's all we have today.
Wait.
Your necktie is crooked.
Oh, thanks.
I'm just a background guy with nothing going for me,
and yet...
Crouch down a little.
The class gyaru ended up being my mock wife.
She really is cute. It's no wonder she's popular.
Staring at my chest like that all the time is creepy as hell.
SQUEEEEEEEEZE
I wasn't! Y-You've got it all wrong!
Take care out there, Jiro.
Sometimes, I fall under a delusion...
What if I really was married to Watanabe?
And we're done!
Don't forget to take out the recycling!
Guess I'll give it everything I've got again today.
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
Oh, Jiro-kun.
Good morning!
Hey, you're here early.
I've got class duties today.
Huh? Wasn't it me and Hamano today?
Oh, crap! Did I get the days mixed up?
Class Duties
Mei-chan has a club leaders' meeting after school today,
so she asked me to take over for her.
For real?
We haven't done class duties together since middle school, huh?
Th-That's right.
This is crazy! It can't be real! I'm insanely lucky today!
Class Duties
Sakurazaka Yakuin
Thanks, Mei-chan.
So, your plan to jump him first thing in the morning failed?
I had no such plan!
Sorry.
But why not just tell him how you feel? We're talking about Yakuin here.
I know it'd work out for you. No problem.
Jiro-kun... doesn't think of me that way.
Uh, yeah, no matter how you look at it, he definitely does.
I've never seen him even talking with another girl.
That's just it.
Up until now, it's only been me.
He didn't know any other girls.
Well, since I've given you this chance by swapping class duties with you,
you should take action!
If you want to make him notice you, you'll have to at least kiss him.
Ki—
If you keep dragging your heels, that mock wife of his might jump him instead.
Kidding! I'm just joking.
Be more confident in yourself.
You're a great girl.
You feel better now, right?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Got a cold?
Bet someone's talking about you.
Cut it out.
You sure are popular.
Speaking of rumors,
apparently about ten pairs have started dating now.
What? So the "practical magic" really does exist.
Well, when you spend every day together...
They're just getting caught up in the mood of it, that's all.
Huh? What is it?
Akari-san, you've been watching Yakuin a lot lately, haven't you?
What? What are you talking about?
I'll be cheering you on no matter who you love,
but I might have a hard time with Virgin-kun.
Wha—
Akari's so pure. In a way, someone of his type would be sort of reassuring.
Better than getting snagged by some creep.
What? That's not happening.
It's obvious that Minami-kun is the peak of humanity.
So she's still stricken with the Minami bug, huh?
Well, I guess we'll just leave it at that.
I'm telling you...
Japanese History, Complete Collection World Atlas Collection North America World Atlas Collection South America World Atlas Collection Asia European Culture
Is that the last of it?
Yeah, it is.
I'm sorry to have made you carry so much.
Not a problem! It's totally fine!
Thanks, Jiro-kun.
Sure.
So all that's left is cleaning the blackboard, right?
Yeah.
This brought back memories, huh? Like being back in middle school.
Don't just say "yeah" and stop!
That ended the conversation!
Think of something to talk about... Something...
I can't think of anything...
Jiro-kun, since we're talking about it, do you remember Hatae-sensei?
The science teacher.
Huh? Oh, the one with the crazy clothes?
Yeah, him! I ran into him at the grocery store the other day.
He was wearing a bright red aloha shirt. I recognized him right away!
For real? That brings back memories.
I guess he hasn't changed, then.
Jiro Today Where are you? I'm gonna go shopping. Come with me Why hasn't he read my message yet?
This makes it seem like I really want to go shopping together.
Jeez...
Oh, that's right! He's got class duties!
Jir—
Why am I hiding?
Sorry!
Jiro-kun, close your eyes and lean down a little.
Huh? Is this a dream?
Close my eyes and lean down a little?
What's going on?!
Huh?
You had chalk dust on you.
Thanks!
No worries. I'll go beat these, okay?
That was a close one!
And holy crap, I'm creepy!
So very not okay!
Class Duties Yakuin
Sakurazaka
Even after we were together for a whole day, this is where we are.
I knew I wouldn't be able to do it!
I'm sorry, Mei-chan!
Sakurazaka
So nothing happened in the end...
But if I'd confessed my feelings back in middle school and been turned down,
we wouldn't have been able to talk today like we did.
I'm so dull and boring.
If she's got a memory of me tucked away somewhere,
I should count myself lucky!
What're you being all melancholy about?
I made too much hot milk.
Want some?
Oh, I'll have some, then. Thanks.
You seem down.
Not really.
Did things go well with Sakurazaka-san?
Oh, you know... Well enough.
You suck at lying, you know that?
Shut up! If you know, then don't ask!
Poor thing. There, there.
Stop making it worse!
The night sky is so damn bright.
You're right! You can see more stars than you'd expect!
Right? It's pretty, huh?
Wow!
I bet the stars would look even prettier if I was with Minami-kun.
Well, sorry it's just boring old me.
Though I'm sure the stars would feel honored to have Tenjin-kun looking at them.
Hey, try calling me by my first name.
That's hot!
Well, come on. "A-ka-ri"!
Where'd this even come from?
I don't want to!
So you call Sakurazaka-san "Shiori," but you call your wife by her last name?
That's just because...
Sh-Shiori is... you know. It's just different.
You're embarrassed to call a girl by her first name!
That's our virgin for you! Number 1 in Japan!
I'm not falling for that.
Boo.
But I guess it's fine.
I really like my name, you know?
I like how it means "light" and is written using the character for "star."
I don't really know why, but sometimes I lose confidence in myself, you know?
At a time like that, if you happened to be by my side,
and called me by my name...
I thought it might feel comforting, that's all.
So practice it before that time comes, okay?
Aka...ri.
It's just... I mean, my name's so plain.
If I had a cool name like that, I'd never live up to it.
But... yours is nice.
I think the name "Akari" suits you.
I'm sorry, Watanabe-san. Let's just pretend that never happened.
No.
Huh?
Again.
And besides!
Me calling you "Jiro" while you use my last name is sort of irritating!
What do you mean, "irritating"?
It's like I'm the only one in love here!
That's a bizarre reason!
Huh?
In love?
It's not... It's not like that.
It was hypothetical... f-for the practical.
No, um... I'm sorry, too. I sort of jumped to conclusions.
I-I've just never had anyone say anything like that to me before.
G-G-Goodnight!
G-Goodnight.
She has Tenjin! There's no way she meant it like that!
Stop reacting like that, you idiot.
God, I hate this!
What do I do?
I'm so confused.
Around this same time every year,
with the marriage practical underway, we see a drop in concentration,
but it's particularly pronounced this year.
Which is why we will immediately begin having special tests.
Just like the regularly scheduled tests,
any students who fail will take supplementary lessons.
Seriously?! I'm a serial offender when it comes to failing!
But this time, the scores of the married pairs in the practical will be combined,
And depending on your pairing, you could get a major handicap.
and supplementary lessons will be taken together, as well.
My wife's gonna kill me. What?! That's just inane!
What? It's sold out? Talk about a letdown.
The test will be next weekend, and married pairs must take supplementary lessons together.
Why'd they even list it? That's so misleading.
Hang on.
Depending on the subject, I'm below average!
Make the most of your time after school by assisting each other.
This is so not funny!
It goes without saying that Shiori and Tenjin will get high scores.
If I get failing grades...
Hey.
Ass in the air, bitch.
She's gonna kill me!
Karaoke? Yeah, I'll go! Yay!
Wait.
We're gonna sing until we're hoarse!
Is Watanabe good at academics?
Until we're hoarse? Just how much stress have you built up, exactly? She comes to class, but she goes to hang out with friends every day.
She couldn't be...
Hey, it's Jiro!
Buy us some fabric softener. The one with the green flowers.
Sure... H-Hey, I wanna talk later about the academic performance tes—
Oh, sorry!
I got invited out to karaoke today.
Apparently, we'll be singing with some guys from some boys' school.
What? Does that bother you? Tee-hee!
Are you jealous?
No!
You're fine for the test, then?
Totally fine!
It'll be fine. Everything'll work out somehow.
"Somehow"?
Aren't there subjects you're not as good at, or areas you don't understand?
Areas I don't understand, huh?
Hmm... What were the areas again?
Watanabe, look me in the eye and say that to me.
I-If I start working hard tomorrow...
it'll be fine.
Let's head home.
I can't! They asked for me.
Look, what if you have to take supplementary lessons?
You'll end up even farther from Tenjin!
Yeah, but...
But nothing!
You can hang out with your friends anytime!
It's not like that!
It's the guys who asked for me, not my friends.
That's harder to turn down.
Guys? Well, I'm asking for you here, too.
Let's go, Watanabe.
All right! I get it already, okay?
This sucks.
You're way too desperate about this.
Just because Sakurazaka-san's involved...
Oh, I get it! I just have to go like this!
All that's left is applying it in practice.
You're amazing, Shiori.
You make it so easy to understand!
Man, these special tests...
You're probably feeling good with Tenjin as your partner,
but there were a bunch of pairs who were panicking about them.
But you pick things up quickly, so you'll be fine!
I'm confident when it comes to sports,
but with academics, not so much.
But I feel like I might just manage this. Thanks!
I'm glad.
As thanks, I'll give you a lecture on how to plan for things of that other type.
What other type?
The kissing type.
Mei-chan!
Man, I laughed so hard about what happened two days ago.
Oh, come on!
Yakuin being the way Yakuin is, and you being the way you are...
Stop talking about it!
By the way, last time...
I don't wanna do this anymore! I need a break!
You've only solved a handful of problems, though.
This is bad.
She picks things up fast when I teach her,
but she just fundamentally hates studying.
Come on, let's just try for a little longer.
I can help you a little with math, and we can tackle the rest together, okay?
Yeah?
For Sakurazaka-san's sake, right?
Huh? Sorry, what did you say?
Nothing.
Hey, Jiro. Let's do something more fun than studying.
What do you want to do?
Whatever you want to do, I'll do it with you.
Well?
What shall we do?
S-Study! We're going to study!
Ugh. Study, study. My ears hurt.
My plan failed.
Listen—
You're so dense.
What made you think a blatant strategy like that would work?
I swear...
Hey, Watanabe. You did this right up to here.
Really?! Yeah.
Try solving it like you did the one before it.
Um, so... 2x is t, right?
So this comes first...
Oh, man! I think I get it!
It...
It's over!
You worked really hard!
We made it further than I thought we would.
I told you it wouldn't be a problem, didn't I?
I might seriously be a genius.
Yeah. You might be right.
She's the type that improves through obvious praise.
Wh-What? I really do think that!
Thanks, Jiro-sensei.
Just kidding!
Your heart just started racing, didn't it?
Guys seem to like that sort of thing. Why is that?
How am I supposed to know?
Come on. Let's get this cleaned up and have something to eat.
Okay. Let's do that, Sensei.
What is this? She's really pestering me a lot today.
So how about that one?
Did that make your heart race?
My heart did not race, then or now.
Stop that! Come on, just clean up!
It's infuriating.
You're just Jiro, but you're better at academics than me.
At least get a little wound up. I feel like I'm losing here.
Get wound up? Look, this isn't about winning or losing—
Huh?! Wait... H-Hey!
Then how about this?
Is your heart racing now?
You're ignoring me again! That really pisses me off, you know!
Remember!
Remember that grotesque scene from the movie you saw yesterday!
Wait!
You're always sneaking glances, right?
Go on. You can look.
Shit! Not this again!
Don't you dare lose, me!
Why...
Damn it!
Hey, the sound of your heart is pretty wild right now.
It's pounding so hard.
It is.
Welp, you lose. Too bad for you.
Wait, huh?
Hurry up and get off me.
Why does your face look so serious?
You can't, okay?
Wait... Your hand!
Are you listening?
I said you can't!
Jiro...
Wait, Jiro!
Your nose is bleeding!
Oh my God! You're adorable!
Damn it! Whose fault do you think this is?
I really messed up!
Thank you, nosebleed! You saved me.
And anyway...
You've been acting weird all day.
Only because you're so desperate not to let Sakurazaka-san leave you behind.
What?
You seemed so impatient and panicked. I just wanted to get you to take a breath.
I'm not working this frantically just for myself.
The sooner you can pair with Tenjin, the better, right?
You're the one who always earns us points.
I'm the one who holds us back.
I mean, I'm sure you'd have done well no matter who you were paired with.
I know how much you've helped me.
I figured, with something like academics, I might be able to help you a bit, too,
even at my level.
Don't try to act cool with a tissue stuck up your nose.
Shut up! Would you just let that go already?!
Don't say anything about it at school!
Jiro If we keep going like this and reach A rank,
and Jiro and I change our pairing...
For the rest of my life, I'll never say "Welcome home" or "I'm back" to Jiro again.
And these clothes that smell of the same fabric softener
will each take on different scents.
But that's the right choice, isn't it?
Because all of this is only study.
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
I got a lower score on our modern Japanese test than Akari did!
Underlined 3 "What can be gained from finding something more enjoyable than studying? Imagine it and write about it."
"Imagine something more fun than studying and write about it."
What kind of question is that?!
Hey, Jiro. Let's do something more fun than studying.
Self-control!
Nothing I came up with was appropriate to write!
Next Time A Male Virgin, but No Female Virgin. Next time, "A Male Virgin, but No Female Virgin."