Come in.
Morning.
Good morning, Yakuin.
The curling iron's still hot, so be careful, okay?
Okay.
Did she call me by my last name?
Feels like it's been ages since she did that.
Sorry, Yakuin.
We ran out of coffee, so it's hot milk today.
Okay.
She really is calling me by my last name.
It doesn't seem like she's angry with me or anything, but...
Oh, yeah. They're gonna start posting the midterm updates today, right?
Yeah. They're gonna come through the app, right?
We studied hard for the special tests, so we should be in a good place.
Thanks.
Oh, jeez.
You've got some bedhead here, Yakuin.
I'll fix it for you later, okay?
S-Sure.
Oh, that's right!
Aside from using my last name, she's acting normal...
or, actually, in a really good mood?
Look! Sachi gave me these chocolates yesterday!
She said it's the super fancy stuff!
Let's eat them together tonight!
Sure.
I can't wait!
What is this?
What's going on?
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
girlfriend suddenly calling you by last name
What?
Why are you searching for that?
Did you find yourself a girlfriend?
Yeah, right.
It's about Watanabe.
What?
You're trying to use real-life crowdsourced knowledge on Akari-chan?
You of all people?
Whose side are you on?
Actually, do you and your wife argue?
We sure do!
Not long ago, she was irritated all day.
So I asked, "Is it your period?" and patted her tummy,
and she wouldn't even talk to me for a while after that.
You are a shining example of how to get a woman to hate a man.
That's right. Bow down to me.
Actually, I wish my wife would just tell me things.
If she said she wanted me to leave her alone, I would.
Will do Read I'm buying shampoo on the way home. Which do you want?
It'd help a lot if they'd just say something.
Exactly. You can pick
I'm sorry I wasn't mindful enough to notice.
But I just can't see you that way.
That's all right!
I'm in love with you, Mei-senpai!
Looks like the rumors were true.
What do you mean?
Apparently, Hamano Mei is super popular with the girls.
There was a time when everyone was talking about it.
Huh...
Wait, what does sneaking around like this say about us?
Thank you for falling in love with me.
Your feelings make me super happy.
Come on. You've gotta smile so you can find someone a lot better than me.
Then, just once...
Please call me by my name!
All right.
Once I let you go, you can't cry anymore, okay,
Manami?
Okay.
I don't know why, but I feel a tremendous sense of utter defeat.
Same.
"I'm sorry I wasn't mindful enough to notice," huh?
It's no use!
I thought it over all day, and I still don't get it!
What is it that I'm supposed to notice?
Why is she calling me by my last name?
Please call me by my name!
...if you happened to be by my side,
and called me by my name...
Nah, that can't be it.
It can't be... Right?
I'm back!
She's back.
Should I try calling her by name just to check?
But if I'm wrong, it'll be embarrassing as hell!
Hey! Yes?!
Did you see the midterm updates?
N-No, but... right now, that's not really... Look at our ranking!
7th Kasugahara Kyo Sangamori Hatsune 8th Yakuin Jiro Watanabe Akari 9th Sanada Nobuyuki Honda Matsuko E-Eighth?!
That's right!
For real? For real!
For really real?
For really real!
We did it!
Oh my God, we did it! I'm so happy!
Yay!
B-B-But first, can I take my shower?
Oh.
This shampoo was definitely the right choice!
It smells so nice!
And it says it'll make your hair super silky.
Wouldn't that be hilarious? A super silky Yakuin.
She seriously isn't calling me by my first name anymore.
I really like my name, you know?
I'm gonna start the hair dryer now.
Akari.
Yakuin, it's not too hot, is it?
Hey, Yakuin?
Akari.
Huh? Wait...
I wasn't... That was...
What is it, Jiro?
Huh? Wait, did I actually... hit the nail on the head?
A-Akari.
What is it, Jiro?
So she really did want me to call her by her name?
Wait...
What?
Akari. Jeez...
If you don't need anything, don't say my name like that.
Crap. I'm gonna start grinning.
Akari.
Stop. Don't look at my face right now.
Th-There's no need to be that embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed!
That's hot! Okay, you're not embarrassed! Of course you're not embarrassed!
Hot! Hot, hot, hot!
I mean, we are technically a married couple, so...
Huh?
I'd prefer if you'd keep calling me "Akari."
That's how...
I like it.
We only have a little longer to go,
so please just indulge me, Jiro.
That's right.
Things will eventually go back to the way they were.
She'll go back to being Watanabe, my classmate.
Kasugahara Kyo Sangamori Hatsune Yakuin Jiro Watanabe Akari Sanada Nobuyuki Honda Matsuko For real?
That way! This is bad, Shiori!
Defense! Defense!
If you don't commit to doing something, you're gonna lose Yakuin!
Th-This again?
You didn't make any progress when you had class duty together.
At this rate, it'll all be over before he even notices anything.
People like Yakuin tend to go where they're pushed.
If you want to date him, you have to do more than his wife is doing!
Th-That's easy to say...
It's possible that they've at least kissed already.
If you let your guard down, they might end up doing even more than that.
M-More than that?
For now, I'll get things set up for you.
Oh, crap!
Heads up!
Hey! Shiori!
Is she okay?!
Oh, shit...
Shiori collapsed?
She's resting in the nurse's office. You should go see her.
Huh? Me?
You got something else to do?
No, but... I mean... I don't really have a reason to go see her.
Do you need a reason to check on someone who's unwell?
Are you embarrassed to say you're worried about her?
If you don't want to go, that's a different story.
But if you're just trying to protect some weird sense of pride, just go.
Here. Take this with you.
I just don't get it, Shiori.
What do you like about a coward like him?
Oh, yeah! I sent Yakuin to you. Read Mei-chan! This is too sudden!
You can do this, me!
Excuse me.
Huh? Where's the nurse?
Jiro-kun?
Shiori?
You came to see me?
Come on in.
O-Okay.
Are you feeling better now?
Yeah, thanks. Sorry for making you worry.
But I'm happy you came to see me.
Um, Hamano sent these. I'll leave them here.
Huh? You already have some.
Oh, Minami-kun brought those.
Oh, right. Yeah, that makes sense.
You're married, after all.
It seems like things are going well.
Huh?
With you and Watanabe-san. You made it to eighth place, right?
Oh... Nah, it's more like things are finally working out.
We're always arguing, so we lose points a lot.
That sounds nice.
I kinda want to try arguing with you, too.
Why?!
Well, I've known you for such a long time,
but I've never seen you angry before.
If I became your wife, would I be able to see that, too?
Oh, I'm just talking about the practical!
R-Right.
I've been feeling anxious.
I'm in high school now, but I still get nervous around boys.
I'm a pain to deal with, huh?
Not at all!
But all the girls around me keep getting more and more mature,
and I'm still a child.
So things with Tenjin haven't gotten... more mature?
Like, you know... kissing or whatever?
We don't do that kind of thing!
And even if things went that way with the person I loved,
I'd be terrible at it, and they'd get sick of me.
That wouldn't happen!
Someone's first time is always precious.
If it was me, I'd be happy no matter what form it took!
H-Hey... You said before that
if there was anything you could do to help, you would, right?
Y-Yeah.
Will you do me the favor I'm about to ask?
Huh?
I want you to practice with me.
K...
Kissing.
I-If you don't want to, that's totally okay!
Sorry for just springing that on you!
It's an imposition, right? I mean, you have Watanabe-san now...
Why? Huh?
Why me?
You're the only one I could ask to do this. I'm sorry.
I don't mind at all.
We can practice, but, um...
I'm probably not very good at it.
Y-You're seriously okay with it being me?
If you would, I'd appreciate it.
Th-Then...
Oh, gosh, my heart is racing so fast!
So is mine.
That makes me happy. Our hearts are racing together.
I don't think it's possible...
but if Shiori... is actually serious about me...
But if you're just trying to protect some weird sense of pride, just go.
That's right! I have to go for it!
If I don't go for it now...
Wait, Jiro-kun!
Let's not do this after all!
We're not married. It probably wouldn't be right.
Excuse me.
Let me take a nap here, Sensei.
Wait, no one's here.
Ugh! You're at school, you know!
Sorry for bothering you!
S-Sorry!
That was an accident!
Y-Yeah, I know. It's okay.
So, um, Jiro-kun, I'll be okay on my own now, so...
R-R-Really? Th-Then I'll get going.
Can I hang out with Sachi and the others after school? Will you be able to find something to eat? Jirooooo!
Please answer me!
Don't ignore me, you idiot.
Akari! So this is where you've been.
Sachi? Weren't you going to the nurse's office to skip class?
I tried, but it wasn't gonna happen.
When I went in, other people were there already.
Between the curtains, I could see the shoes of a guy and a girl.
And the bed was creaking.
Huh? What do you mean? You think they were doing that?
What else could a guy and a girl be doing to make a bed creak?
Seriously, what the hell are they thinking?
Sorry. Shiori collapsed, so I was in the nurse's office. Got it. Jirooooo! Please answer me!
Sorry. Shiori collapsed, so I was in the nurse's office. Got it.
No way.
Akari? What is it?
Jiro...
Let's eat it together!
7/5 Wednesday Akari's pretty late.
Sorry we couldn't do an all-nighter You seem down. What's wrong? If it's something you can talk about, tell us Natsumi's worried about you, too
Oh, Mikkun, you were about to clock out, weren't you?
Sorry. I just need whipped cream on this.
Got it.
The one who ordered it is a serious gyaru,
but she seemed kinda down, so you can give her a little extra for free.
Really?
Thank you for waiting!
Please enjoy at your leisure.
It's so good! And sweet!
Huh?
Extra whipped cream on the house. Hope it cheers you up.
Huh? Oh, crap! Did it show on my face?
How embarrassing!
Oh, I get it. I'm...
feeling depressed.
That guy's actually really nice.
Did Jiro really do that with Sakurazaka-san?
He said she's his first love, right?
Having your first time be with your first love would make anyone happy.
Just because Jiro and Sakurazaka-san are together now
doesn't mean anything's changed.
Jiro and I are a married couple right now, that's all.
It's nothing more than that, and yet...
If I open this door right now,
I feel like there'll be a Jiro there that I don't know.
Is he already asleep?
Why are you sleeping there?
And why are all your dirty clothes scattered everywhere?
I told you not to roll up your socks like that!
What am I, your mother?
Come on! I'm stepping on the pedal, but it won't...
Argh!
Got it!
Ugh!
I'm gonna start throwing my dirty clothes everywhere, too!
Are you okay with that?
And if you're going to sleep, sleep in your room!
And you could at least vacuum!
7/5 Wednesday I just found out... Those chocolates have whiskey in them! You haven't eaten them, have you?!
Learn to cook something!
And I'm shouting here, so wake up already!
Jeez... My depression just disappeared.
The table's all messy, too...
You were waiting for me?
Idiot.
Hey, Jiro? Are you listening?
You're really not gonna wake up?
Are you alive?
Your wife is taking off her clothes here, you know.
Hey, Jiro...
Is this what you did in the nurse's office?
Or was it...
something far beyond this that I don't even know about?
Did you go off and become an adult without me?
I'd hate that. Don't leave me behind.
You know, I really will cheer you on in your love.
So just for now, while I'm your wife, could you wait?
Please, Jiro.
Ow, my arm...
Wha?!
Why? Why is she sleeping next to me?!
And what happened to her clothes?!
Good morning, Jiro.
What's wrong? I said good morning.
Hey!
Huh? What? What's wrong with you?
That's what I want to ask you!
Wh-What happened to your clothes? I can see everything!
You didn't even realize it?!
I have a ton of questions, but first, please put some clothes on.
We can talk after—
What's the point now?
You're the one who took them off of me.
Wow, you're scum! You really forgot what happened last night?
H-Hang on. Time out.
What?
You really don't remember! What a jerk!
Even after all you did to me...
Don't!
After "all" I did?!
Wait, wait. I have absolutely no memory of anything.
Does that mean we did it?
That we went as far as it's possible to go?
No, wait.
She has Tenjin, but she'd let me have her body?
Yeah, as if things would ever get like that between us, anyway...
Except they already did!
Wait!
I'm not a virgin anymore?
Huh? Wh-Why are you asking me?!
Let go of me, you idiot!
Oh, s-sorry.
If we really did do it, I'd be absolute scum not to remember, right?
I mean, it probably...
wasn't just my first time.
Hey, Jiro...
Was last night your first time?
Last night?!
If it happened... then it was.
Really?
If you're lying, you don't get any dinner.
It was. Why would I lie about that now?
I see.
So it was.
Also... sorry.
Huh?
I mean, since I was a virgin...
I probably put most of the burden on you.
It must have been difficult and painful because of m—
I was lying.
Huh?
I lied.
Isn't that obvious?
Of course it was all a lie!
Talk about hilarious!
You...
You've gotta be kidding me!
You fell for it!
You should know I'm not that easy!
Jeez... There are some lies that are just not okay, you know!
But, yeah... Yeah, of course.
Come on. You could act a little disappointed, couldn't you?
Well, of course I'm disappointed.
I mean, I'm still a virgin.
Ow! That hurts! Ow! Ow! Ow!
I'm sorry!
Of course you'd never do that with a guy like me, right?
I was being presumptuous!
It's not that!
I'd never do that when I know you have Sakurazaka-san.
Huh? What did you say?
"I hate that my first time was with a girl I don't even love."
"I wish it had been Sakurazaka-san instead."
That's how you felt, right?
Hey, I can't hear you!
Why don't you just say that?
I don't know what you're saying!
I hate you, Jiro.
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
What a nice feeling. I'd like to fall asleep just like this.
Jiro-kun, come to me.
Shiori!
There's one Jiro-kun.
Shiori! And two Jiro-kuns.
There's three Jiro-kuns. Shiori!
Next Time Fireworks, but No Embrace. Next time, "Fireworks, but No Embrace."