Did something happen between you and your wife?
What d'you mean?
Every break, you run away and hide here.
It made me wonder if you didn't want to see her.
N-Nothing special happened.
Huh...
I mean, Akari's been the same as always since then.
Oh, the Slie Pinca Dold spell works on that guy.
Sleeping cuddled?
No, not "sleeping cuddled"! He said "Slie Pinca Dold"!
It's going to take a while to move all these.
Those going to the trash pickup site?
They must be heavy. We'll carry them.
Peace!
Ohashi-san! Takamiya-san!
Thank you.
Leave it to us! This'll be a piece of cake for Sachi!
Hey, you're helping, too!
But for real, who would dump all this on just one person?
I didn't have anything else to do, so I ended up saying I'd do it.
Sakurazaka-san, you're way too nice.
Hey, you there! Slouchy!
Come here.
She means you. She means you.
Otakus first.
That's you, too!
I mean both of you! You're both slouching!
No, no, no!
Get over here and help Sakurazaka-san.
Shiori?
You gotta be kidding me!
Can someone so slouchy even be of service, I wonder?
Natsumi "Of course you can! We're relying on you, my man♥" Of course you can! We're relying on you, my man!
Taking out the trash is life! Taking out the trash is everything!
I'd whale in a game to take out trash!
I worry for his future.
You, too, Akari's husband. Stop spacing out and get moving.
Yes, ma'am!
How should we divide it up?
The two of us will take these three. One for me, two for Glasses-kun.
Absolutely! Okay.
I can handle these two, so Sakurazaka-san and Slouchy-kun can take that big one.
T-Takamiya-san, please, let's carry it together!
...carry it together!
Sob.
Jiro has suffered near-fatal damage
Hey, what's wrong? Got the runs?
The restroom in the gym is the closest.
My heart...
Huh?
Sorry. I guess most people wouldn't want to do this as a guy-girl pair, huh?
Pair up with me instead.
Okay. Thank you.
Um...
Josui Ryokuchi
Yum! This new flavor is amazing!
Right? Right?
It's yummy, right?
It's crazy good, isn't it?
Hey, do you...
My question will take a while, so you go ahead, Sachi.
Well, mine isn't exactly light conversation either, so I'll go after.
Mine's probably heavier.
No, no, I know mine is...
Just play rock-paper-scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Go ahead!
Akari! Huh?
So... If you're being totally honest, what do you think of Yakuin?
You've avoided the topic all this time...
But it's not like you don't feel anything for him at all, right?
I-It's not... I mean...
Oh, jeez. She's not even denying it anymore.
I get it. I mean, I'm your best friend.
That's why it really hurts to watch you right now.
Akari, what about Minami-kun?
Before, you'd squee just from seeing his name on the class roster.
Minami-kun and Sakurazaka-san seem to really be hitting it off.
It makes me wonder if I'm just getting in the way.
Of course you're not!
Everyone's just trying to look good for the practical.
But...
And it's not like we're saying you shouldn't turn toward Virgin-kun.
I just don't want you to get swept up in the mood, that's all.
That's right.
Yakuin might've been like that with any wife, even if it wasn't you.
Just give it some calm, rational thought.
Even if it wasn't me... You're right.
Akari! Cheer up!
That's right. Quit moping around.
It's not like those two are your only options, anyway.
That tickles, you two!
I'll see you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow!
Hey, Virgin-kun and Sakurazaka-san haven't started dating, right?
I don't know. It seemed like something happened between them, but...
Akari doesn't know about Sakurazaka-san's feelings, right?
What if Akari says she really wants to be with Virgin-kun?
That'd be fine.
It's not like Akari has to give up on him because of Sakurazaka-san.
I just want her to give serious thought to what she wants for herself.
Akari is so conscientious of the people around her. How does she truly feel?
Sachi...
If only something would happen that could serve as a decisive moment for her.
I'd support her in any way I could.
There's gotta be some way...
Ohori Park Fireworks Festival 7/17 (Mon.) *Rain date will be the 18th.
This is it!
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
Hey, it's way too loose!
It's supposed to be tight enough that you can only fit your index finger in it.
Come on, pull it as tight as you can.
That's easy for you to say...
Virgin.
That has nothing to do with this.
Jeez... It's not like you have to go out of your way to wear a yukata, y'know.
What? Minami-kun will be there. I can't just wear what I usually wear!
Even if Tenjin's there, it's not like you'll be walking around the place together.
Girls can't afford to relax, even for a moment.
All she ever does around me is relax.
Is she saying she doesn't see me as a man?
Oh, the way this one's tied is pretty cute! Like what happened the other morning.
She leaves herself way too open.
If I untied this cord, she'd be left in her underwear! Oh, this one's nice, too!
Does she realize that?
Hey, Jiro, which do you think...
And what is that about?
Oh, nothing.
You're not looking me in the eye, though.
Please don't let it bother you.
Come on, do it right! My love is on the line here!
This is next.
Introduction: Tying Simple and Pretty Obi for Yukata Kai-no-kuchi knot For both men and women, this is our recommendation for couples who want to match! Simple and impossible to mess up, it gives a snappy impression. With its air of maturity, it's a perfect match for chic yukata.
Which one do you like?
And you can't say "all of them."
What? I don't really know...
Maybe this ribbon bow style?
What? It's so childish, though!
Anything but that, I think.
Why'd you even ask, then?!
Unlike you, Minami-kun likes more mature styles.
Oh! I'll do this one, thanks!
Yes, of course. As you command.
Why am I doing this?
What's this? Are you jealous?
I am not.
Oh, really? What a brat.
Well, you just watch the fireworks from the veranda all alone and lonely.
And while you're doing that, Minami-kun and I will have a nice mood going.
Now, tie me already.
Oh, right! Don't bother calling me if you get lonely.
I'll be busy with Minami-kun.
This little...
We've cleared the hard part.
All that's left is to tuck in the ends.
I'll turn it around to the front so you— Okay, go ahead.
What?
Huh? What do you mean, "what"?
Nothing.
Okay, suck in your stomach for me.
Wow, that's a super rude thing to say.
Okay, then, excuse my hands.
What're you saying that for?
Don't give me that!
Yukata fabric is so thin, I can feel everything.
How she's soft, warm, so slender it seems like she might snap in half...
Damn it! Why am I the only one affected by this?
I'm so pathetic.
Akari, it's not too tight?
No, it's fine. Thanks, Jiro.
It's so pretty!
We have to get yakisoba, right?
Really?
Akari, you look so cute!
Forget lucky underwear, you wore a lucky yukata!
It looks so good on you!
Light blue was totally the right choice.
Thanks.
The pink looks great on you, too, Natsumi!
Akari, you always compliment me! I love you!
I complimented you, too!
Oh, that's right.
I love you!
Tenjin and the other guys should be here soon.
Other guys? Like Terafune?
Yeah.
We've laid the groundwork with everyone other than Minami-kun, so it's all set.
Isn't that great, Akari?
What? You told everyone?! That's super embarrassing!
It's not like it matters now.
Delicious Deluxe Chocolate Bananas Piled High Yakisoba
Everyone knows you squee over Minami-kun.
That's right. And that's why no one tries anything with you.
Are you serious?
Don't worry, Akari.
If you can get even a little closer, that's enough, right?
Don't let it get you all worked up! We're all here with you.
And you look super cute in your yukata!
That's right! Be confident!
Yukata...
The yukata that Jiro dressed me in.
I'll show Minami-kun this yukata.
If I fall even more in love with Minami-kun,
and spend every day obsessed with him like I did before...
Will I still be able to pull off my married life with Jiro
and cheer him on in his love, too?
Thanks.
I'll give it my very best!
Takamiya!
Huh? Where's Minami-kun?
We're really sorry!
Hey. What do you mean by that? Explain yourselves.
Well... he said something about his job calling him in to help.
What?!
The fireworks festival brought in a flood of customers.
He's just such a nice guy...
I couldn't stop him.
If Tenjin isn't coming, there's no point to the rest of this!
You're right. Sorry.
Forget about me introducing you to any girls.
Takamiya-sama!
Watanabe, I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it! Actually, I'm sorry you got dragged into this.
Thanks, Terafune.
Um, I'll treat you to something as an apology.
What do you want to eat? Or we could go look around and—
Okay, get going!
Takamiya...
Three yakisoba, two takoyaki, and three candied apples.
Then we'll call it even.
Takamiya-sama!
We are grateful and overjoyed!
What?
At 7:30 pm, Terafune was arrested on suspicion of hitting on someone.
Hey, get off!
I'll go! Let go of me!
Crap.
We will now begin the interrogation.
Cut it out!
Huh... Didn't know that about Terafune-kun.
Sorry, Akari.
We said we'd create a chance for you, and things turned out like this.
It's okay. Thanks. I'm grateful to all of you.
Delicious Chocolate Banana Deluxe
Let's ask the boys to get us something sweet, too!
Yeah. We should go after them. Wait here a sec.
Okay.
I wore a yukata because Minami-kun was coming.
I put a lot of effort into my makeup,
and I spent more time than usual on my hair.
I thought this would be my chance.
I thought if I saw Minami-kun here, something would change.
So why did I feel relieved when I heard Minami-kun couldn't make it?
I love Minami-kun.
Chasing after Minami-kun like I used to...
Simply acting out the role of Jiro's wife like I used to...
But... things changing to be like that is still...
It's still scary to me.
I know I'm not the one next to either of them.
Once I make a choice, I'll never again...
Terafune, just give up already.
No! Watanabe said she likes fish.
Pretty sure she meant she likes to eat fish.
No, no! Why am I getting all discouraged now?
Everyone's cheering me on! I have to do my best!
I know! I could stop by where he works!
Wow, look!
Hey, he's pretty hot!
Do you think he's famous?
But the girl with him seems like his girlfriend.
Minami-kun...
He said he was working...
Maybe it's time to bow out gracefully and give up.
But why?
I've tried so hard.
We're back, Akari!
We've got fresh baby castella cakes!
What's wrong? You look a little pale.
Do I? Sorry, I just...
I'm not used to wearing a yukata. It might be too tight.
Really?
Akari, you should go home for today.
Minami-kun isn't coming anyway, right?
That's right! Let's start looking for the next chance!
Yeah.
Thanks.
That was a heck of a crowd.
Maybe we should've taken a different street. Sorry.
It's okay. The shortest route to the supermarket is through the shrine grounds.
Well, my work is that way.
Sorry to make you go shopping all the time.
I'll go buy the heavy stuff tomorrow.
Don't worry! Just leave it to me!
We're a married couple, after all.
We have to do our best to help each other out!
And this is something that will affect your college references.
You really saved me here. Thanks.
Be careful out there!
A fireworks festival...
I wonder if Jiro-kun went...
Oh, man.
Did I catch a chill after my bath?
And while you're doing that, Minami-kun and I will have a nice mood going.
I wonder if Akari's got a nice mood going right now.
What'd she mean by a "nice mood," anyway?
Like... a kiss?
Holding hands, hugging, kissing...
They're the same things, but if Tenjin does them, will it make him her boyfriend?
What about me, then?
If we change our pairings and I'm not her mock husband anymore,
then I'll be...
...a friend?
No. Just a classmate?
We've spent every day together for so long now,
but with the "married couple" aspect gone...
Will there really be nothing left?
I did all that stuff with her before Tenjin, though...
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Just who do I think I am?!
I make myself sick!
Tch. Who's calling me now, when I'm feeling this gross?
Watanabe Akari Cell Phone
Huh?
I can answer, right? I mean, she's the one calling me.
Hello?
Hello, Akari?
Jiro...
What's wrong?
I knew I wasn't...
Where are you right now?
Where are you? I'll be right there.
Jiro... I'm sorry.
Jiro!
Oh, for crying out loud... I'll run!
Tell me where you are!
What? Why'd she hang up?!
Wait, wait, wait! Hang on a minute! Come on!
All Missed Call Log Watanabe Akari Watanabe Akari Home Watanabe Akari Kamo Home
Watanabe Akari Calling
Come on, answer!
Huh?
Akari...
I'm sorry. I ended up coming home.
After you did my yukata and everything...
I'm so sorry!
Everyone worked so hard for me, but...
I'm sorry.
Everyone...
I'm sorry!
Welcome home.
Welcome home, Akari.
I'm back, Jiro!
Sachi and Natsumi both told me this yukata looked nice on me.
I'm glad I wore it.
But doesn't the obi make it hard to breathe?
You're home now. Why not take it off?
That's sexual harassment. Gross.
That is not what I meant!
Hey, do I look cute in a yukata?
What do you think of the wife you dressed yourself?
I still think the ribbon bow would suit you better.
Aw, hiding your embarrassment again?
Are you still pouting?
You are jealous, aren't you?
I don't know.
Whoa, what is it?
Give me your hand.
Wait...
What? Huh?
Um... Go ahead.
W-With what?
Go ahead and do a ribbon bow.
Do what you like.
O-Okay, then...
Aren't you done yet?
The fireworks are gonna be over, clumsy.
No one asked you! This is only the second time in my life I've done this.
Uh-oh.
What? Did you mess it up?
No, just...
No matter how many times I look at what I'm supposed to do next, I don't get it.
Well, there's a video version, too.
Let me see.
That was close!
Th-This is... It's not...
Huh?
H-Hey, let—
Hey, Jiro...
Stay like this and say my name.
If you say my name,
I feel like I'll be able to try again.
Sometimes I lose confidence in myself, you know?
Akari.
Yeah. More.
More.
Akari.
Wow, it's beautiful! And so cute!
Wow, that's amazing! Wait, what is it? A peach?
It's a heart, you dork!
It's upside-down.
Oh... Oh!
Jiro...
Thanks.
For not asking me what happened today.
We're married. Helping each other out is what we're supposed to do.
I didn't ask because I didn't want to know.
I'm rooting for her to be with Tenjin, but...
Oh, it's upside-down again.
When I heard her crying through the phone...
When I realized that she'd come home...
Why did I feel relieved?
The timing didn't work out this time,
but there'll be more fireworks festivals this year and next year.
Yeah. Thanks.
We're a married couple,
and marriage means pledging to spend a lifetime together.
But for us, there is no "next year,"
so this small view we see from this veranda...
is probably the first and last fireworks show we'll watch together.
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
Actually, I had a yukata all prepared, too.
That works surprisingly well!
You didn't need to say "surprisingly"!
It's nice! Super nice!
Too bad, though. We're all done here!
Um, actually, I had one ready, too!
Brava! Brava! It's just too good!
Next Time An Entreaty, but No Reassurance. Next time, "An Entreaty, but No Reassurance."