We haven't been able to really talk since then.
How long will things stay this way?
There's no way things are going to stay this way forever, right?
The Forest of Courage is also known as the Forest of Decision.
Chloris
As the hero, which princess is fitting for you?
Make the wrong choice and this kingdom will be destroyed.
What the heck...
Lancia Well, I believe in you!
What the heck?
Lucky Item Lucky Color Overall Luck ★★☆☆☆ It will be easy to feel depressed. If you can stay positive, you may be able to brighten everything around you, as well. Luck in Money ★☆☆☆☆ You may have unexpected expenses. Luck in Love ★★☆☆☆ Think about what it is that's most important to you. Luck in Academics ★★☆☆☆ Your hard work will likely pay off. Beware of careless mistakes.
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
Y-You're sure?
I can look?
Ready, and... Seishun Academy Marriage Practical Homepage for Students Latest News Practical Overview Practical Schedule Schedule Procedures Personal Page Regarding Furnishings Points to note regarding furnishings for use during the practical. Those with questions should consult their homeroom teachers. Latest News
1st | 2nd | 95 | Kaizuka 3rd | 92 | Miyajidake Asahi 4th | 90 | Shingu Aoba | Hakozaki Umi 5th | 88 | Sanada Nobuyuki | Honda Matsuko 6th | 86 | Tenjin Minami | Sakurazaka Shiori 7th | 85 | Shimoori Wakahisa | Omuta Katsuki 8th | 84 | Fukuma Terukuni | Jouno Honami 9th | 82 | Kasugahara Kyo | Sangamori Hatsune 10th | 82 | Okubo Osamu | Shuto Kyoko 11th | 81 12th | 81 13th | 79 14th | 60 | Mitoma Kiyokazu | Nakahara 15th | 59 | Shirakihara Chitose | Kaneda Sue
Th-Thirteenth.
What?! Just three places short?
We were super close! That's so annoying.
I'm pretty sure the pair in fifth started dating last month.
For real? Well, there's no way we could beat that.
Oh, well. No helping it now.
I'll be counting on you for another month,
darling.
Yeah.
I dunno...
I never found out what happened that day,
and Akari went back to normal, like nothing had happened.
But she cried so much, and she still seems determined to switch partners.
Is that how much she wants to be with Tenjin?
Jiro!
This is terrible!
What is it? What happened?
That creep showed up! Help me!
Huh? What creep?
Please! Please! Please! Hurry! Hurry, Jiro!
Calm down, Akari! Who showed up?
A spider!
Don't barge in on me in the bath over a stupid spider!
I'm stark naked here!
What do you mean, "a stupid spider"?
And who cares about a body like yours?!
Whoa! That counterattack hit hard!
I don't care!
Just do something about that creep right now!
I can't go back into the living room!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Get me my towel and clothes first!
So?
Where is this spider?
It... It's gone!
Stay calm. How big was it?
About this big.
Huh? That's tiny!
It doesn't matter how small it is! I can't handle spiders!
All right, I get it. Sorry.
I'm dealing with hugeness myself.
It might suddenly show up again.
She's cute when she's meek and quiet.
Hey, I want a snack.
Go ahead.
Come to the kitchen with me!
Huh?
Okay. Forward!
But that's only when she's being meek and quiet.
I ate too much.
Gotta do my nails next.
How long should I stay here?
Well... until the spider shows up and you catch it.
Oh, come on. If you call for me, I'll come right back.
Then I'm calling for you now.
It'll be scary if it suddenly shows up again.
The feel of that hugeness against my leg!
Jiro...
Come with me?
Are you serious?!
Jiro! You're there, right?
Yes.
Cover your ears, okay?
Right! The sound!
Jiro? I said I'm here!
You can still hear!
I was just about to cover my ears!
It's no good.
I can't help but imagine what's happening in there, even if I don't want to!
Please, hurry up and come out!
While my conscience still lives!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'll go, too. Saves me having to come back.
I know! It'll just take a few seconds!
I wish I could die!
This is the worst! The absolute worst!
Asking him to come to the bathroom with me is so wrong!
I'm so embarrassed, I just want to disappear.
But since it's Jiro, I figured he'd come with me instead of saying no.
I'm glad Jiro's the one with me.
I'd never be able to ask Minami-kun for something like this.
Here.
Let's head back.
You washed your hands?
Freshly washed!
Thanks.
And after the way she was just minutes ago...
I really am living with a gyaru.
At first, I thought it'd never work, but somehow or other...
Hey, I want some of that, too.
Oh, there's some in the freezer.
What?
I can't go. I'm scared of the spider.
I just want one bite, so yours is fine.
Then I'll get a spoon and—
Nope!
I can't use my hands.
Oh, you're thinking about indirect kisses now, aren't you?
You're such a little kid!
Why would you bring that up right now?
Come on, hurry up.
It's yours I want, Jiro. Give it to me.
O spirits, calm thyselves! Jewels! Jewels! Family jewels!
Here.
What?
You used to like chocolate ice cream.
Do you think we're getting to be more alike?
Hey, did something good happen to you today?
Huh? Nothing in particular. You're funny.
Hey, hypothetically speaking...
If you and I had met somewhere else, what do you think would've happened?
We never would have talked, probably.
What? You're so mean.
I think I might've wanted to meet a Jiro who wasn't my husband.
Huh?
You'd be hilarious, with all your gloom-and-doom on display.
But we don't have anything in common, so we wouldn't have hit it off.
The other pairs are probably like that, too.
But the fifth-place pair are dating, right?
Well, they're sort of an exception.
Should we try dating, too?
Just kidding!
Look! I think my nails turned out really nice today!
Do you mind if I turn on the TV?
G-Go ahead.
Why did I think about it for a second?
There's no way she was serious about it!
If she were serious, she wouldn't say it so casually.
If she were serious...
what answer would I have given her?
If we weren't a married couple...
If we'd met while I had no idea Jiro loved someone else...
Spider! Spider! Spider!
Huh?! What?!
You mean that? It's tiny!
Please! Do something, Jiro!
W-W-Wait! Wait! Wait!
Akari! Let go!
Jiro!
Th-This hot sensation on the back of my hand...
A-Akari...
Why are you just sitting there spacing out?! Hurry up and do something!
I will! I'll do something! Just please let go of me!
Here.
I'll buy this for next time.
No.
What do you mean, "no"?
I don't wanna touch it after I've sprayed it.
You say that now, but what if your next husband hates bugs?
It won't be a problem.
Because if I call for a certain someone, he'll come right away.
Right?
Don't go skipping a beat there, heart. She's just toying with you!
Well, goodnight, darling!
Seriously... What am I, your bug exterminator?
In any case, I'll be counting on you for a little while longer,
Akari.
Shiori? What's wrong?
Minami-kun.
Something on your mind?
You can talk to me about it, though I'm not sure if I'll be any help.
Thank you.
Remember when I told you about my friend who reunited with a boy she liked?
Yeah.
It's about that friend again...
Okay.
Th...
They kissed.
I-It was an accident! They aren't dating yet.
But she doesn't know how to face him anymore.
I don't—I mean, she doesn't know how the boy feels about her,
so she's worried that he didn't like it.
But the thing is...
Worrying about it made her realize that she really does love him.
All she can think about ever since then is that kiss.
But she doesn't know if she wants to tell him how she feels or not.
She's scared.
What should she do, Minami-kun?
Minami-kun?!
Y-Your tea!
Sorry, I wasn't looking.
It's okay. The sofa didn't get wet.
Here's a towel.
The reason she's scared must be because she's hoping for something, right?
But...
If there's any possibility it'll work out, I think she should try for it.
The guy she wants to tell is the one she was able to fall in love with.
It'd be a waste if she ended up being too late, like me.
I'm sorry, I...
No, no, I didn't mean it like that.
I don't want you—
I mean, your friend—to have any regrets,
and if I can help with that, I'd like to.
Thank you.
I'm glad I got paired with you, Minami-kun.
Oh, I know. What about asking if he hated the kiss?
That's just impossible!
For your friend?
"I think you should have more confidence."
Tell your friend I said that.
Confidence?
I'm telling you, you should be more confident in yourself, Shiori.
This off-the-shoulder look is nice!
Yakuin's a guy, so he'll like this kind of thing.
Come on, Mei-chan! We're picking something out for you right now!
But I just know you'd look cute if you wore it.
I know you would, since you have such nice legs.
What do you think of this?
I've got tan lines from my running shorts.
Then how about this? I think the red would suit you!
Stop thinking about what would suit me.
I want you to pick out something you like.
What? But...
After all, you'll be the one who sees it.
I'll be wearing it the next time we go to the movies.
So make me into a me that you like.
I think I know how your fans feel now!
Anyone who dates you will be very happy!
You say that so easily.
There are people I can't make happy, you know.
I'm sure those people just don't know how wonderful you are, that's all.
Maybe I'll go tell them.
How 'bout instead, you go hug Yakuin, tell him everything's gonna be okay,
and teach him why it's great to be an adult.
Then just throw yourself at him right there!
M-Mei-chan, not so loud!
Hamano!
Hey, what's up?
Hey.
I have an interview for a part-time job today, so I won't need dinner.
Okay. Is it that place you mentioned before?
Yeah. The place by the station, with the star.
Is that the same place as Minami-kun?
That's right.
Oh! I've been worried since Minami-kun seemed to be working too hard lately,
but I feel better knowing you'll be with him!
Yeah, this guy is surprisingly considerate.
Ooh, a rare word of praise from my wife.
Hey! Oh, right.
I asked Tenjin to do karaoke with me after dinner, and we'll be going all night.
You two wives should eat together and stay over at one of our places.
Stay—
Sometimes spending the night together is nice, right?
Just the two of you and a hot night.
Are you seri—
That sounds nice!
Let's do it, Mei-chan!
Let's have a sleepover!
Huh?
Oh, did you have other plans?
No, but...
I'm not "surprisingly" considerate, I'm super considerate, right?
No one asked for your help!
I never should have said anything to you!
So, that's what we're doing. You two get along, okay?
I swear...
I can't wait! What should we do for dinner?
Yeah, what should we do?
Sorry! Come do a karaoke all-nighter with me after the meeting today I already got the okay from your wife! Then we might see each other at the shop Thanks in advance
Then we might see each other at the shop Thanks in advance Sorry! Come do a karaoke all-nighter with me after the meeting today I already got the okay from your wife! I'll never ask for anything again!!
"I'll never ask for anything again."
Sorry! Come do a karaoke all-nighter with me after the meeting today I already got the okay from your wife! I'll never ask for anything again!! Roger that
Yes!
I'll never ask for anything again!! Roger that You use the "I'll ever ask for anything again" line too much
This is how a married couple should be!
Man! It's so good, it's gonna make me cry!
Sugi
Are you listening, Teranishi?
Mikkun is...
My name is Terafune.
He's working hard at my café so he can move out after he graduates!
Why, you ask? Because Mikkun and his older brother...
share a super tragic fate—
You've had too much to drink, Kamo-san.
And I told him all about this last year.
Yeah?
It must be rough having ikemen DNA, right?
Even your siblings are your rivals!
Makes us glad we're not ikemen ourselves, right, Terashima?
My name is Terafune.
Tenjin, what's your older brother like again?
Do you guys look alike?
He's just average.
An ikemen should never say that! It insults all of us non-ikemen!
As punishment, drip-filter your handsomeness and let us drink it!
Right, Terasaka? My name is Terafune.
I sure am glad my little brothers are average, though.
Excuse me!
Can we get some water? Wait. Are they less than average?
Of course. Coming right up. Oh, you have little brothers?
You didn't know? That guy with the glasses in our class is one of them.
The one who's friends with Yakuin.
Yakuin...
Sure is a small world, huh?
I was so sure it wouldn't work out.
Why are they thirteenth?
I met Watanabe first!
What does he have that I don't?
Height and luck! That's about it!
Ugh. Those flaws are pretty fatal...
What?! Stories of unrequited love?!
Those are my favorite!
Come on, Kamo-san. Drink some water.
Okay, it's decided!
We'll spend the night at my place.
You can use the bed, Mei-chan.
Huh? N-No, I'll be fine sleeping on the floor.
No, I can't make you do that.
Oh! Should we open up the sofa in the living room and sleep together instead?
T-Together?!
No, no, no.
Let's take a bath together, too!
A-Are you all right, Mei-chan?!
Sorry.
It went down the wrong pipe. I'm fine.
Oh, but I wanted to see the old photos in your room.
You have them up, right?
Like the photo from when we won that tournament in middle school!
I don't have anything like that. All my pictures are of family.
Oh, really?
Do you have any old photos up?
Just a few.
I'm looking forward to seeing little Shiori.
Oh, but it might be a little embarrassing.
Most of them are of me and Jiro-kun.
Of course.
Oh, sorry.
My mom asked me to do something right away,
so I have to go to my parents' house from here.
What?
Sorry! We'll do this another time, okay?
Chef's Kiss Marinated Maguro Bowl Chef's Kiss Marinated Maguro Bowl
Why did I end up eating dinner with the same guy I see all the time?
You're the one who invited me.
Well, my wife told me out of the blue to go eat out somewhere.
I bet she's complaining about me right now.
But things are going all right, aren't they?
Well, we aren't as cozy as someone sitting in thirteenth place.
Cozy?
What do you mean, "kissed by accident"?
This isn't a harem anime.
How can an accident cause lips to lock with lips?
I don't know what to tell you...
Hey, Jiro-chan. It's almost summer, you know.
Stupid Kamo. The way you use your hands is so naughty. I don't want a fake wife. I want a girlfriend!
I want to try falling in love in the 3D world, too!
No, I don't need love!
If I can escape virginhood, that's good enough!
If you have to actually say that, you know it's impossible.
Shut up, you traitor!
We had an alliance.
And you call yourself my childhood friend? Blast you!
Are you drunk or something?!
Hey. What's come over you all of a sudden?
I will cancel out your luck-based lechery.
What?
It's no use. When I'm alone, I can't help but...
Kiss
Chef's Kiss Marinated Maguro Bowl
I will use my lips to overwrite the save data.
Hey, be serious! You're scaring me!
That won't just overwrite! I'll suffer a physical crash!
It's simply an equivalent exchange.
No!
Huh?
Shiori, it's not like that.
Ow!
Keep the change!
There's something wrong with me.
Imagine reading "Chef's Kiss Marinated Maguro Bowl" as just "Kiss Bowl."
Shiori!
Jiro-kun?
You've got it all wrong! It wasn't like that at all!
Huh?
Do you mean...
I just don't want you to misunderstand...
It was just kind of an accident...
Yeah. I know.
I'm the one who should apologize.
It's fine. I'm not bothered by it at all.
Thank goodness!
Kamo was panicking and slipped into some weird mode.
Huh? Why are you mentioning Kamo-kun?
Huh? Well, Kamo was the one I was goofing off with at that restaurant.
You were at a restaurant?
Huh?
I-I'm so sorry! I think I was talking about something else!
I'm sorry! I was mistaken, too.
Seriously, please forget all of it.
Th-That looks heavy.
Oh... I ended up buying too much.
I'll carry it. Oh, if you don't mind, that is.
What? Y-You don't mind?
Sure.
If Shiori and I were married, this is what it'd be like.
I'm probably the only one thinking that way, though.
It's funny, isn't it? When we're like this, it's almost like we're marr—
Huh?
Nothing!
What? Come on, tell me.
It's nothing.
Thank you for carrying this with me, Jiro-kun.
When I was in the nurse's office, too...
I'm sorry about that!
It was all my fault. I'm really sorry.
No, I—P-Please listen, Jiro-kun!
You don't have to apologize.
Huh?
I mean...
Uh...
I was the one who asked you to teach me.
And... I-I learned a lot.
That that's what a... k-kiss feels like...
It wasn't that I didn't want you to.
So... thank you.
She's saying all this to me,
and she still wants me to just stay her friend forever?
It's even warm at night now, huh?
Shall we head home?
Let's head home, Jiro-kun!
Soon, summer will be here again...
The third summer since Shiori came back.
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
Sadaharu-kun, kiss me.
What is this? A dream?
Your first kiss is with me! Right, Sada?
She called me Sada.
Why are you getting in the way? You're the one getting in the way!
Huh? Wait. You two?
A little further and... Smooch.
Why did I wake up there?!
Next Time More Than a Childhood Friend, But Not True Love.
Next time, "More Than a Childhood Friend..."
"...But Not True Love."