So on that note...
Don't get carried away because it's summer break.
Summer Vacation
Subject to Point System
Vacation
Interviews with students requiring supplementary lessons
Until July 31st, conduct your lives with a firm awareness that you are being graded.
The practical with Akari is on the right track,
but now we're at the end of the term with a lot left unresolved.
It'd be unfair to Akari to let this drag on into the second term.
I wonder what Shiori's doing for summer break.
She's probably going home in August, but...
It's summer! It's the ocean! But I have no money... Come Work With the Best Team! Resort Café Dining Hall and Kitchen Daily Wage 8,000 yen Short-term lodging! All hair colors allowed!
A live-in summer job?
Yep.
The café where my older brother works is running a pop-up shop as a summer event.
It's only for three days, but he said they're short-staffed.
So you'll be doing this live-in summer job?
That's right.
Summer brings limited-time events to dimensions other than this one, too.
And I really need the money, so I instantly told my brother I'd do it.
The work is easy. It's the kind of thing they'd give to temp workers, after all.
Huh...
So I sent in an application for you, too.
What?!
What the hell were you thinking? I can't serve customers!
And living there would suck for a guy with communication issues.
I know that!
That's exactly it!
An introvert like me is never gonna survive alongside those lions known as "party people"!
So why are you going?
Summer is Marin-chan's season!
I have to get ready for this year's swimsuit gacha!
I really need the money! For Marin-chan's sake!
For Marin-chan's swimsuit gacha!
Marin-chan!
Here. You dropped this.
Hey, thanks...
Shiori!
Th-Thanks.
You're welcome.
Wait, that flyer...
Mei-chan and I applied for that job, too!
I wanted to see what having a part-time job is like.
What? Really?
Yeah! And it's short-term, so it doesn't overlap with the summer intensives!
For real? I did, too!
Kamo-kun, you applied, too? Then we're the same!
Yeah! For some reason, this summer, I wanted to be of use to others.
Jiro-chan and I are gonna work ourselves to the bone!
Hey!
What?
Jiro-kun, you'll be there, too?
Y-Yeah.
Yay! I have even more to look forward to now!
Let's all work hard together!
It's win-win, right?
A live-in job with Shiori...
You cut your hand?
Pain, pain, go away!
I feel lonely all by myself.
Can I sleep with you?
My heart is pounding so fast, I can't sleep.
Adrenaline is flooding across my synapses!
Jiro-chan!
Huh? What?
I'll tell my brother about the job.
You go get your wife's okay for this. I've already gotten it from mine.
Right.
Though I'm sure yours won't have a problem with it.
While her husband's away, she might bring in some other guys!
Ah, welcome home, darling!
Do you want to join in?
Oh, how dirty! Eek!
She's not like that.
Oh, my.
I hope this job will turn out to be a decisive moment for you.
Huh? Say what?
Nothing. Just talking to myself.
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
It's criminal to be so shy
Intelligence and wild fancies, tick tock, just pick a mood
A drizzle from a patch of blue sky
No less than supreme
A maiden's heart zigzags, cute and invincible
The wild ringing of bells
What percentage does "like" have to hit before you can call it "love"?
Hold me so tightly that I fall asleep
A daydream that seems like fiction
Give me a kiss that breaks the expectant silence of the play
Give that indecision a tight embrace, too
My heart hurts and hurts,
racing unpredictably with joy and excitement
It's TRUE FOOL LOVE! Hold me tight!
Be brave, my darling
It won't all be happy and fun
It's all up to us
ONCE MORE SMILE, TWICE MORE CHIME
Please look my way, darling
Please notice my pure love for you
I'm home!
She's not here? Oh, right. She was going to be out today.
Welcome home, Jiro.
What? You're back alrea—
...dy?!
What do you think of this?
Wha? Wh-Wh-Wh...
Is it cute?
You're totally red!
Over a simple swimsuit? That's hilarious!
Uh, no way! A simple swimsuit?
A "simple" swimsuit?!
What happened to all the fabric?!
We're planning to go the beach, so I bought this with Sachi and Natsumi today.
But do you think it's too risqué?
I bought two suits, so maybe I'll wear the other one.
You're staring, you perv.
Anyone would stare at that.
I think that might be a bit much. There's not a lot of fabric there.
Why are you talking about fabric?
The ties here are cute, aren't they?
Look!
Eek! That lustful look in your eyes!
Oh, gosh! I'm so scared!
You told me to look!
Also, those are my clothes!
Aw, what's the problem?
And is it Takamiya and Ohashi you're going with?
Will there be guys?
What? Does it bother you?
It's not that.
If you're wearing that, I'd actually feel better if you had guys with you.
Oh, uh, sorry. Who do I think I am, right?
It's just... I don't think it'd be as safe with just girls.
It's not like that. I'm going for a part-time job.
A job?
A short-term job at a café near the ocean.
I'll be staying there starting Friday next week.
Really? There are a lot of those this time of year.
But that's perfect. I got a live-in job, too, and I wanted to talk to you about it.
What? You got a part-time job?
I can't picture that.
I can't, either. But Kamo says I have to.
You two are joined at the hip, huh?
Don't say that! It's creepy! And...
Oh, right. Shiori will be there, too.
Apparently, she and Hamano applied together.
You're trying hard to make things work with Tenjin, right?
I just thought I should start making some moves, too.
Oh.
I see! So that's what your real goal is, huh?
What a relief!
If I left you on your own, you'd end up eating just cup noodles,
so I was on the fence about whether I should go or not.
Really? Sorry.
So we'll be apart for a little while, then.
Yeah, we will.
Well? Does it make you feel lonely?
Huh? Why?
Oh, right. Sakurazaka-san will be there, so you won't be lonely.
Huh. I see how it is.
Where's this coming from?
Say you'll miss me.
Say it!
We're married, aren't we?
Oh, come on! The job is only for three days!
And we'll both be at our parents' places for the whole month of August, right?
Then it's even more important! Say it!
Why are you angry over this?
Get off of me!
Nope. I dunno why, but I'm pissed now.
I won't move until you say it.
Say you'll feel lonely without me!
Hey! Are you kidding me?!
Say it! Say it! Hurry up!
Akari-san! I'm begging you! Please have mercy on me!
You're making me feel lonely...
I'm recharging my battery.
Shit!
This electrical discharge...
It's now or never.
All done!
Huh?
We won't earn any points for three days, so we have to earn them now.
Right.
Anyway, Akari-san... Aren't you going to change out of that?
What? Do you not like this swimsuit?
No, that's not what I'm talking about here.
I'm not sure which one I want to wear, so tell me!
Do you like it or not?
Well, I can't say I hate it, I guess.
I am a guy, after all.
It's normal for me to like it.
Then I think I'll wear the other one after all!
Hey! After you made me say all that?!
Say...
Go to the beach with me sometime, too.
Huh?
This suit...
will be just for you.
It's sad that you'll only be seeing girls and the ocean because of a job, anyway.
You were probably planning to spend your whole summer break gaming, right?
No one asked for your opinion!
I'll make sure your summer is a fun one. Be ready for it, okay?
Why is she saying these things?
Come Work With the Best Team! Resort Café Dining Hall and Kitchen Daily Wage 8,000 yen Short-term lodging! All hair colors allowed!
Wait, don't tell me your part-time job is...
Huh?
It's summer! It's the ocean! But I have no money... Come Work With the Best Team! Resort Café Dining Hall and Kitchen Daily Wage 8,000 yen Short-term lodging! All hair colors allowed! Resort Café Dining Hall and Kitchen Daily Wage 8,000 yen Short-term lodging! All hair colors allowed! Hiring staff for our STAR BOX COFFEE shop on the beach!!!! This season has come again this year! We'll be setting up our super-popular summer-only beachside shop this year, too! Whether it's with your friends or with your significant other... please apply!
What?!
There it is!
Yay! Going ashore!
This sun is too dazzling for a shadow-type like me.
And yet you seem to have come here all ready to go.
This summer will be full of dramatic ups and downs! And I'm gonna have them, too!
I've gotta work hard.
And this is the lodging house.
The whole place is reserved for us as long as we're working here.
The guys are over here.
And the ladies' rooms are on that side.
Minami-kun really is cool, isn't he?
For now, leave your stuff here,
then come to the café for training.
Okay.
Well, then...
Wow, it's pretty big.
There are futons here!
This is a nice place.
The ocean's so close!
Yoo-hoo!
Cut it out. You're not gonna hear an echo.
I love you, Ryou-kun!
And we don't need confessions of love like that, either.
Oh, right! I brought a deck of cards.
Let's all play together tonight.
Hamano-san, you two, too!
Count us in!
Me, too!
Let me play, too!
Let's go.
Okay.
Oh, wow! This uniform is so cute!
It is! It actually gets me hyped up!
This isn't the right size, is it? Maybe I'll ask for a different one.
It's fine! Just show it off! It's summer, after all!
What are you talking about?
This is so cute, it makes me feel embarrassed.
I don't usually wear this kind of thing.
Yeah, even your regular clothes are on the sporty side.
But I'm really happy we get to match!
It suits you. You look very cute.
Th-Thanks.
So, I think that does it for the explanation of the shop.
Basically, you'll be split up between the kitchen and the floor.
If you have a preference, grab an employee during the lunch break and tell them.
Yes, sir.
Man, I am seriously glad you're here, Jiro-chan.
The design of this place is so stylish, it makes me feel all insecure.
You sure put a lot of effort into the outfit you wore here, though.
I didn't think you owned anything like that.
My brother bought them for me a while back. He seemed weirdly energized.
He said something like, "You should take a lesson from my friendliness!"
Seriously, who gave him a compliment like that?
Still, I might have a chance with one of the gyarus!
One must never fail to be prepared!
And I have my lucky item from this morning's fortune, a knotted misanga bracelet!
All that's left is a chance encounter with a girl who loves enka music.
I just sort of stumbled into this summer job,
but getting to spend two nights with Shiori when we aren't married...
This chance might never come again.
Jiro-kun, are you choosing the kitchen or the floor?
The kitchen... probably.
I wouldn't be comfortable helping customers.
M-Maybe I'll pick the kitchen, too.
I'd feel better with someone I know.
So... want to work the kitchen with me?
Okay?
For real?
Y-Yeah.
Amount Due
Choose Transaction
Credit
E-money
QR Code
Let's see...
Think you'll be okay?
Yeah!
Right here.
Oh, I see! Thanks!
You learn fast. That really helps me out.
I can tell you're really listening.
I'm so happy!
Then, once you've given their card back...
I give them the receipt, right?
Hey, so...
Earl Grey Milk Tea
Can toppings be added to this one, too?
Hey!
Hey, are you listening, teacher?
Oh, look at this! I bet Akari would love it!
Which one? Show me!
Just kidding!
You are idiotically easy to read. And you are an idiot.
Hey! If you're gonna make fun of me, I won't teach you how to do the work!
You're way too uptight. You'll never win over any girls like that.
But you know...
It's gotta suck when the one you're in love with is in love with your friend.
If Akari and Minami-kun start dating, what'll you do?
That's not gonna happen.
How do you know?
Call it... intuition.
There's no way that brain of yours contains any kind of intuition. Spit it out.
That's kinda harsh.
If you don't tell us, I'll be angry!
And Natsumi-sama is scary when she's angry.
They're making a lot of noise. What are they so excited about?
G-G-Give! I give up!
They seem like they're having fun.
Sorry for making you work the kitchen with me.
Don't be!
I mean, this is my chance to work a part-time job with you!
Thanks!
You say that, but the one you'd rather be with is over there, right?
M-Mei-chan!
Just look at his back. That's the back of a useless man.
You need to show off the fact that you're a woman.
It may have happened by coincidence, but this is a rare chance, right?
Escape the role of "childhood friend." This summer is clutch time!
Okay.
Yakuin!
Sorry, Yakuin. Could you get that thing up there for us?
Shiori can't reach.
Oh, um... Please?
Sorry, Jiro-kun.
It's fine. Which one?
Um...
This syrup.
Jiro-kun?
Oh, sorry! That one, right?
Yeah.
You've got this, Shiori.
Jiro-chan! I got a new bottle of soa—
Hey! What is this, gravity?
Sorry. Could you move these cardboard boxes first?
Of course! If I can be of help.
Hup!
A misanga...
Do you like enka, by any chance?
What?
Sorry.
Thank you, Jiro-kun.
No, thank you.
Moron! What are you thanking her for?!
Is this one of those ones you put cream and stuff on?
Yeah! Want to practice together?
It's hard getting this in there.
Yeah, but this is your first time, right?
Y-Yeah.
It's all right. Try doing it slowly and gently.
Okay.
That's right. Like you're tracing softly along the edge.
Do it slowly and gently.
There's no need to rush or panic. It's all right to go slow.
That's right. Gently.
Like this... maybe?
Yes. It's all the way in.
That's right. Now keep it there and start moving, slowly.
Oh! No, don't rush.
That's it.
It might be better if you went in a little straighter. Like this.
Jeez, Jiro-kun!
Huh?! Uh, s-s-sorry!
You look like you have a mustache!
D-Don't laugh! It's on your face, too!
What? Oh, no! Where?
Oh, not there. It's in a totally different spot!
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
J-Jiro-kun, wipe it off.
That tickles!
Sh-Shiori, if you don't hold still, I can't get it off.
Jiro-kun's hands are so warm.
Escape the role of "childhood friend."
This summer is clutch time!
Okay. I think I got all of it.
Jiro-kun...
Please look at me. I mean, really look.
Shiori?
Jiro-kun, I...
Shiori? Is something wrong?
So sorry to bother you when you're in the middle of something.
What size were we supposed to get, again?
No idea. Let's bring them all.
Jiro-kun was so surprised. Is he disgusted by me now?
She really looked like she hated that! I might've blown it already.
Sorry for bothering you!
Take your time and enjoy!
I, um... I'm so sorry!
No, I'm the one who should be sorry.
Don't panic, me. Everything's fine. There's still plenty of time.
I was able to tell him a little, Mei-chan.
It's all right. Summer's only just begun.
It's all right. Everything's all right.
This isn't that other summer!
Going forward, if I want to be closer to Shiori than anyone else is,
things can't stay as they are.
I have to get past this "childhood friends" thing I've upheld all this time!
Jiro-chan!
Did you bring your swimsuit?
Huh?
The ocean!
It's gorgeous!
This rocks!
What a glorious view!
This will restore my vision!
In multiple ways.
To be at the beach with sunny extroverts while I'm still in high school...
I guess life's worth living after all, Jiro-chan!
It's clear that we're in a different group from them, though.
But Akari's one-piece bathing suit is unexpected.
Usually, she shows so much skin.
Though that's cute in its own way.
This suit...
will be just for you.
No, it can't be...
That's not possible.
It couldn't be...
No, it's not possible, right?
Huh? Jiro-kun, where are you guys' swimsuits?
You're not going in the water?
Because you can't swim?
We didn't think we'd get free time, so we didn't bring our suits.
We thought it'd be enough to just look out at the ocean.
Yeah, right. I bet you were just staring at the gross parts of the girls.
Th-That's a horrible thing to say!
They're not gross! They are sacred areas!
Thank you for giving us these gifts to take home with us!
Are you stupid?!
I don't quite understand, but, u-um...
If you'd like, why don't we go over there together?
What do you say?
A hotel?!
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
In this night when everything begins to overflow
I match my stride to yours
The clock hands stop, charmed by a fleeting curse
The answers always slip away
All I want is to do it over again
If I did, would this unsettling gloom inside me disappear?
I want to know where my heart is hiding
One day this will end
I know that
And I know the signs of discord
Turn them inside out
Don't let them pile up
I don't want things to stay unfinished like this
In this moment when I've deceived you on a cosmic scale
I want to give love a try
Everything begins to overflow
On this day when we don't know how much time is left to us
I want your thoughts to drift toward me fondly, again and again
Ta-da! What do you think of this swimsuit?
Ooh, sexy!
If you want a suit for when everything's on the line, this is it!
Whoa, it's basically just string.
What if it comes untied?
Well, if that happened, your boyfriend would probably cover for you.
I don't think he'd be that considerate.
Hm?
Who are you talking about?
Huh? Nobody!
Next time...
Next Time
"Already" Has Passed, But Not "Yet."
"'Already' Has Passed..."
"...But Not 'Yet.'"